[{"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "choose the curtain that is above the desk. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "choose the curtain that is over the desk. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "find the backpack that is on top of the bed. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "find the backpack that is on the bed. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "find the backpack that is lying on the bed. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 65], "object_names": ["cup", "mirror"], "question": "find the cup that is below the mirror. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 65], "object_names": ["cup", "mirror"], "question": "find the cup that is under the mirror. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 65], "object_names": ["cup", "mirror"], "question": "find the cup that is beneath the mirror. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 65], "object_names": ["cup", "mirror"], "question": "find the cup that is underneath the mirror. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [32, 4], "object_names": ["stool", "counter"], "question": "choose the stool that is in front of the counter. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [32]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "facing the front of the counter, choose the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "facing the front of the counter, choose the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "facing the front of the counter, choose the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "looking at the front of the counter, choose the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "looking at the front of the counter, choose the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "looking at the front of the counter, choose the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 8], "object_names": ["backpack", "desk"], "question": "select the backpack that is in front of the desk. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "looking at the front of the desk, pick the picture that is on the right of the desk. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "looking at the front of the desk, pick the picture that is to the right of the desk. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "looking at the front of the desk, pick the picture that is on the right side of the desk. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "facing the front of the desk, pick the picture that is on the right of the desk. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "facing the front of the desk, pick the picture that is to the right of the desk. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "facing the front of the desk, pick the picture that is on the right side of the desk. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 11], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink"], "question": "find the backpack that is in front of the sink. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "looking at the front of the sink, select the doorframe that is on the right of it. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "looking at the front of the sink, select the doorframe that is to the right of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "looking at the front of the sink, select the doorframe that is on the right side of it. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "facing the front of the sink, pick the doorframe that is on the right of the sink. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "facing the front of the sink, pick the doorframe that is to the right of the sink. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "facing the front of the sink, pick the doorframe that is on the right side of the sink. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [14, 12], "object_names": ["bin", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, select the bin that is on the left of it. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14, 12], "object_names": ["bin", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, select the bin that is to the left of it. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14, 12], "object_names": ["bin", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, select the bin that is on the left side of it. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 12], "object_names": ["bin", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, select the bin that is on the left of it. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14, 12], "object_names": ["bin", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, select the bin that is to the left of it. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 12], "object_names": ["bin", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, select the bin that is on the left side of it. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, select the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, select the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, select the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, pick the doorframe that is on the left of the scale. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, pick the doorframe that is to the left of the scale. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, pick the doorframe that is on the left side of the scale. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 12], "object_names": ["carpet", "scale"], "question": "select the carpet that is in front of the scale. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, choose the picture that is on the right of it. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, choose the picture that is to the right of it. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "facing the front of the scale, choose the picture that is on the right side of it. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, choose the picture that is on the right of it. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, choose the picture that is to the right of it. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "looking at the front of the scale, choose the picture that is on the right side of it. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "looking at the front of the clock, pick the curtain that is on the left of the clock. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "looking at the front of the clock, pick the curtain that is to the left of the clock. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "looking at the front of the clock, pick the curtain that is on the left side of the clock. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "facing the front of the clock, pick the curtain that is on the left of the clock. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "facing the front of the clock, pick the curtain that is to the left of the clock. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "facing the front of the clock, pick the curtain that is on the left side of the clock. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 18], "object_names": ["backpack", "clock"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in front of the clock. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rounded toe", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "looking at the front of the clock, pick the shoe that is on the left of the clock. What is shape of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "looking at the front of the clock, pick the shoe that is to the left of the clock. What is color of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "looking at the front of the clock, pick the shoe that is on the left side of the clock. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "facing the front of the clock, choose the shoe that is on the left of it. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "facing the front of the clock, choose the shoe that is to the left of it. What is function of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "facing the front of the clock, choose the shoe that is on the left side of it. What is size of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, select the backpack that is on the back of it. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, select the backpack that is behind it. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, choose the backpack that is on the back of it. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, choose the backpack that is behind it. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the backpack that is on the back of the couch. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the backpack that is behind the couch. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "looking the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the stool that is on the right of the couch. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "looking the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the stool that is to the right of the couch. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "looking the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the stool that is on the right side of the couch. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, select the stool that is on the right of it. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, select the stool that is to the right of it. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, select the stool that is on the right side of it. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, pick the stool that is on the right of the couch. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, pick the stool that is to the right of the couch. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, pick the stool that is on the right side of the couch. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, pick the towel that is on the right of the couch. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, pick the towel that is to the right of the couch. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "facing the front of the couch, pick the towel that is on the right side of the couch. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the towel that is on the right of the couch. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the towel that is to the right of the couch. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "facing the couch from the side you sit on it, choose the towel that is on the right side of the couch. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, pick the towel that is on the right of the couch. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, pick the towel that is to the right of the couch. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "looking at the front of the couch, pick the towel that is on the right side of the couch. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [13, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "looking at the front of the refrigerator, select the bin that is on the left of it. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["used for storing clothes or other items"], "object_ids": [13, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "looking at the front of the refrigerator, select the bin that is to the left of it. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [13, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "looking at the front of the refrigerator, select the bin that is on the left side of it. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["rectangular with rounded edges", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [13, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "facing the front of the refrigerator, choose the bin that is on the left of it. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["sits on the floor"], "object_ids": [13, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "facing the front of the refrigerator, choose the bin that is to the left of it. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [13, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "facing the front of the refrigerator, choose the bin that is on the left side of it. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "looking at the front of the refrigerator, choose the cup that is on the left of it. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "looking at the front of the refrigerator, choose the cup that is to the left of it. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "looking at the front of the refrigerator, choose the cup that is on the left side of it. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "facing the front of the refrigerator, select the cup that is on the left of it. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "facing the front of the refrigerator, select the cup that is to the left of it. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "facing the front of the refrigerator, select the cup that is on the left side of it. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "looking at the front of the toilet, select the doorframe that is on the right of it. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "looking at the front of the toilet, select the doorframe that is to the right of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "looking at the front of the toilet, select the doorframe that is on the right side of it. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "facing the front of the toilet, choose the doorframe that is on the right of it. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "facing the front of the toilet, choose the doorframe that is to the right of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "facing the front of the toilet, choose the doorframe that is on the right side of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, pick the table that is on the left of the bed. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, pick the table that is to the left of the bed. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, pick the table that is on the left side of the bed. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the table that is on the left of it. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the table that is to the left of it. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the table that is on the left side of it. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the cup that is on the right of it. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the cup that is to the right of it. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the cup that is on the right side of it. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, select the cup that is on the right of it. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, select the cup that is to the right of it. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, select the cup that is on the right side of it. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, no visible damage or wear"], "object_ids": [161, 38], "object_names": ["picture", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, choose the picture that is on the back of it. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["canvas, wood (frame)", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [161, 38], "object_names": ["picture", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, choose the picture that is behind it. What is material of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [161, 38], "object_names": ["picture", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the picture that is on the back of it. What is texture of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on the wall"], "object_ids": [161, 38], "object_names": ["picture", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the picture that is behind it. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [161]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the towel that is on the right of it. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the towel that is to the right of it. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "looking at the front of the bed, choose the towel that is on the right side of it. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, choose the towel that is on the right of it. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, choose the towel that is to the right of it. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "facing the front of the bed, choose the towel that is on the right side of it. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "facing the front of the oven, choose the bin that is on the left of it. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "facing the front of the oven, choose the bin that is to the left of it. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "facing the front of the oven, choose the bin that is on the left side of it. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "looking at the front of the oven, choose the bin that is on the left of it. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "looking at the front of the oven, choose the bin that is to the left of it. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "looking at the front of the oven, choose the bin that is on the left side of it. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [30, 46], "object_names": ["stool", "oven"], "question": "choose the stool that is in front of the oven. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "looking at the front of the oven, choose the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "looking at the front of the oven, choose the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "looking at the front of the oven, choose the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "facing the front of the oven, select the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "facing the front of the oven, select the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "facing the front of the oven, select the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 47], "object_names": ["bin", "basket"], "question": "choose the bin that is in front of the basket. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 47], "object_names": ["cup", "basket"], "question": "looking at the front of the basket, choose the cup that is on the back of it. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 47], "object_names": ["cup", "basket"], "question": "looking at the front of the basket, choose the cup that is behind it. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 47], "object_names": ["cup", "basket"], "question": "facing the front of the basket, select the cup that is on the back of it. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 47], "object_names": ["cup", "basket"], "question": "facing the front of the basket, select the cup that is behind it. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 47], "object_names": ["towel", "basket"], "question": "looking at the front of the basket, select the towel that is on the back of it. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 47], "object_names": ["towel", "basket"], "question": "looking at the front of the basket, select the towel that is behind it. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 47], "object_names": ["towel", "basket"], "question": "facing the front of the basket, select the towel that is on the back of it. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 47], "object_names": ["towel", "basket"], "question": "facing the front of the basket, select the towel that is behind it. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 48], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in front of the guitar. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "guitar"], "question": "looking at the front of the guitar, pick the carpet that is on the back of the guitar. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "guitar"], "question": "looking at the front of the guitar, pick the carpet that is behind the guitar. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage"], "object_ids": [150, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "guitar"], "question": "facing the front of the guitar, pick the carpet that is on the back of the guitar. What is state of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "guitar"], "question": "facing the front of the guitar, pick the carpet that is behind the guitar. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "facing the front of the tissue, pick the curtain that is on the left of the tissue. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "facing the front of the tissue, pick the curtain that is to the left of the tissue. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "facing the front of the tissue, pick the curtain that is on the left side of the tissue. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "looking at the front of the tissue, pick the curtain that is on the left of the tissue. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "looking at the front of the tissue, pick the curtain that is to the left of the tissue. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "looking at the front of the tissue, pick the curtain that is on the left side of the tissue. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 49], "object_names": ["backpack", "tissue box"], "question": "select the backpack that is in front of the tissue. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 52], "object_names": ["stool", "dish rack"], "question": "choose the stool that is in front of the dish. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "looking at the front of the dish, pick the doorframe that is on the left of the dish. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "looking at the front of the dish, pick the doorframe that is to the left of the dish. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "looking at the front of the dish, pick the doorframe that is on the left side of the dish. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "facing the front of the dish, pick the doorframe that is on the left of the dish. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "facing the front of the dish, pick the doorframe that is to the left of the dish. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "facing the front of the dish, pick the doorframe that is on the left side of the dish. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "looking at the front of the microwave, pick the bin that is on the left of the microwave. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "looking at the front of the microwave, pick the bin that is to the left of the microwave. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "looking at the front of the microwave, pick the bin that is on the left side of the microwave. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "facing the front of the microwave, choose the bin that is on the left of it. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "facing the front of the microwave, choose the bin that is to the left of it. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "facing the front of the microwave, choose the bin that is on the left side of it. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [30, 53], "object_names": ["stool", "microwave"], "question": "find the stool that is in front of the microwave. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [30]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "looking at the front of the microwave, pick the doorframe that is on the left of the microwave. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "looking at the front of the microwave, pick the doorframe that is to the left of the microwave. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "looking at the front of the microwave, pick the doorframe that is on the left side of the microwave. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "facing the front of the microwave, pick the doorframe that is on the left of the microwave. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "facing the front of the microwave, pick the doorframe that is to the left of the microwave. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "facing the front of the microwave, pick the doorframe that is on the left side of the microwave. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 54], "object_names": ["table", "toaster"], "question": "choose the table that is in front of the toaster. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "facing the front of the toaster, pick the bin that is on the left of the toaster. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "facing the front of the toaster, pick the bin that is to the left of the toaster. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "facing the front of the toaster, pick the bin that is on the left side of the toaster. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "looking at the front of the toaster, select the bin that is on the left of it. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [14, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "looking at the front of the toaster, select the bin that is to the left of it. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "looking at the front of the toaster, select the bin that is on the left side of it. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["pine or similar wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [32, 54], "object_names": ["stool", "toaster"], "question": "find the stool that is in front of the toaster. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [32]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "looking at the front of the toaster, select the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "looking at the front of the toaster, select the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "looking at the front of the toaster, select the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "facing the front of the toaster, choose the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "facing the front of the toaster, choose the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "facing the front of the toaster, choose the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "looking at the front of the door, pick the cup that is on the left of the door. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "looking at the front of the door, pick the cup that is to the left of the door. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "looking at the front of the door, pick the cup that is on the left side of the door. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "facing the front of the door, choose the cup that is on the left of it. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "facing the front of the door, choose the cup that is to the left of it. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "facing the front of the door, choose the cup that is on the left side of it. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "facing the front of the door, select the towel that is on the left of it. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "facing the front of the door, select the towel that is to the left of it. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "facing the front of the door, select the towel that is on the left side of it. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [168, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "looking at the front of the door, select the towel that is on the left of it. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "looking at the front of the door, select the towel that is to the left of it. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "looking at the front of the door, select the towel that is on the left side of it. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "facing the front of the shelf, choose the stool that is on the left of it. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "facing the front of the shelf, choose the stool that is to the left of it. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "facing the front of the shelf, choose the stool that is on the left side of it. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "looking at the front of the shelf, pick the stool that is on the left of the shelf. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "looking at the front of the shelf, pick the stool that is to the left of the shelf. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "looking at the front of the shelf, pick the stool that is on the left side of the shelf. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36, 58], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle"], "question": "find the table that is in front of the bicycle. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, pick the bin that is on the right of the mirror. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, pick the bin that is to the right of the mirror. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, pick the bin that is on the right side of the mirror. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [14, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, select the bin that is on the right of it. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, select the bin that is to the right of it. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, select the bin that is on the right side of it. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 65], "object_names": ["backpack", "mirror"], "question": "select the backpack that is in front of the mirror. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, choose the doorframe that is on the right of it. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, choose the doorframe that is to the right of it. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, choose the doorframe that is on the right side of it. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, pick the doorframe that is on the right of the mirror. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, pick the doorframe that is to the right of the mirror. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, pick the doorframe that is on the right side of the mirror. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, select the towel that is on the left of it. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, select the towel that is to the left of it. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "facing the front of the mirror, select the towel that is on the left side of it. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, select the towel that is on the left of it. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, select the towel that is to the left of it. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "looking at the front of the mirror, select the towel that is on the left side of it. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 68], "object_names": ["curtain", "chair"], "question": "select the curtain that is in front of the chair. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "facing the chair from the side you sit on it, choose the backpack that is on the back of the chair. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "facing the chair from the side you sit on it, choose the backpack that is behind the chair. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "facing the front of the chair, pick the backpack that is on the back of the chair. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "facing the front of the chair, pick the backpack that is behind the chair. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking at the front of the chair, select the backpack that is on the back of it. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking at the front of the chair, select the backpack that is behind it. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "facing the front of the chair, select the backpack that is on the left of it. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "facing the front of the chair, select the backpack that is to the left of it. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "facing the front of the chair, select the backpack that is on the left side of it. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking the chair from the side you sit on it, choose the backpack that is on the left of the chair. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking the chair from the side you sit on it, choose the backpack that is to the left of the chair. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking the chair from the side you sit on it, choose the backpack that is on the left side of the chair. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking at the front of the chair, choose the backpack that is on the left of it. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking at the front of the chair, choose the backpack that is to the left of it. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "looking at the front of the chair, choose the backpack that is on the left side of it. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "facing the front of the speaker, pick the curtain that is on the right of the speaker. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "facing the front of the speaker, pick the curtain that is to the right of the speaker. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "facing the front of the speaker, pick the curtain that is on the right side of the speaker. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "looking at the front of the speaker, pick the curtain that is on the right of the speaker. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "looking at the front of the speaker, pick the curtain that is to the right of the speaker. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "looking at the front of the speaker, pick the curtain that is on the right side of the speaker. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 88], "object_names": ["backpack", "speaker"], "question": "select the backpack that is in front of the speaker. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "looking at the front of the computer, choose the shoe that is on the left of it. What is size of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "looking at the front of the computer, choose the shoe that is to the left of it. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "looking at the front of the computer, choose the shoe that is on the left side of it. What is size of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "facing the front of the computer, pick the shoe that is on the left of the computer. What is function of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "facing the front of the computer, pick the shoe that is to the left of the computer. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "facing the front of the computer, pick the shoe that is on the left side of the computer. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, choose the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, choose the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, choose the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, pick the doorframe that is on the left of the switch. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, pick the doorframe that is to the left of the switch. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, pick the doorframe that is on the left side of the switch. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, pick the cup that is on the left of the switch. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, pick the cup that is to the left of the switch. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, pick the cup that is on the left side of the switch. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, select the cup that is on the left of it. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, select the cup that is to the left of it. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, select the cup that is on the left side of it. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [168, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, choose the towel that is on the left of it. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, choose the towel that is to the left of it. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "looking at the front of the switch, choose the towel that is on the left side of it. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, choose the towel that is on the left of it. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, choose the towel that is to the left of it. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "facing the front of the switch, choose the towel that is on the left side of it. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "looking at the front of the pot, choose the doorframe that is on the left of it. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "looking at the front of the pot, choose the doorframe that is to the left of it. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "looking at the front of the pot, choose the doorframe that is on the left side of it. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "facing the front of the pot, pick the doorframe that is on the left of the pot. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "facing the front of the pot, pick the doorframe that is to the left of the pot. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "facing the front of the pot, pick the doorframe that is on the left side of the pot. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [123, 181], "object_names": ["remote control", "pot"], "question": "choose the remote that is in front of the pot. What is size of the remote control ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [123]}, {"answers": ["ceramic", "Ceramic"], "object_ids": [184, 181], "object_names": ["bowl", "pot"], "question": "find the bowl that is in front of the pot. What is material of the bowl ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [184]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "facing the front of the lamp, select the table that is on the right of it. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "facing the front of the lamp, select the table that is to the right of it. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "facing the front of the lamp, select the table that is on the right side of it. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "looking at the front of the lamp, choose the table that is on the right of it. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "looking at the front of the lamp, choose the table that is to the right of it. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "looking at the front of the lamp, choose the table that is on the right side of it. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 4, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "counter", "couch"], "question": "choose the towel that is between the counter and the couch. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 4, 48], "object_names": ["towel", "counter", "guitar"], "question": "find the towel that is in the middle of the counter and the guitar. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 4, 49], "object_names": ["towel", "counter", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the towel that is in the middle of the counter and the tissue. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 4, 68], "object_names": ["towel", "counter", "chair"], "question": "select the towel that is in the center of the counter and the chair. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 5, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the center of the shower and the bicycle. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 5, 67], "object_names": ["table", "shower", "case"], "question": "choose the table that is between the shower and the case. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 5, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower", "chair"], "question": "the backpack that is in the center of the shower and the chair. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 5, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower", "lamp"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the middle of the shower and the lamp. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 8, 11], "object_names": ["stand", "desk", "sink"], "question": "select the stand that is in the center of the desk and the sink. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 8, 38], "object_names": ["stand", "desk", "bed"], "question": "select the stand that is in the center of the desk and the bed. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 8, 47], "object_names": ["stand", "desk", "basket"], "question": "choose the stand that is in the center of the desk and the basket. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 8, 48], "object_names": ["stand", "desk", "guitar"], "question": "the stand that is between the desk and the guitar. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [35, 8, 57], "object_names": ["table", "desk", "shelf"], "question": "find the table that is in the middle of the desk and the shelf. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 11, 47], "object_names": ["carpet", "sink", "basket"], "question": "the carpet that is in the middle of the sink and the basket. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 11, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the middle of the sink and the bicycle. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 11, 67], "object_names": ["table", "sink", "case"], "question": "the table that is in the middle of the sink and the case. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 11, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink", "chair"], "question": "find the backpack that is in the middle of the sink and the chair. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 12, 37], "object_names": ["carpet", "scale", "toilet"], "question": "find the carpet that is in the middle of the scale and the toilet. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 33, 46], "object_names": ["towel", "couch", "oven"], "question": "find the towel that is between the couch and the oven. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 33, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "couch", "door"], "question": "the towel that is in the center of the couch and the door. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 34, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "refrigerator", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the center of the refrigerator and the bicycle. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 34, 58], "object_names": ["stool", "refrigerator", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the stool that is in the middle of the refrigerator and the bicycle. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 34, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "refrigerator", "mirror"], "question": "select the doorframe that is in the center of the refrigerator and the mirror. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 34, 189], "object_names": ["stool", "refrigerator", "lamp"], "question": "choose the stool that is in the center of the refrigerator and the lamp. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 37, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "toilet", "guitar"], "question": "find the carpet that is in the middle of the toilet and the guitar. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 37, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "toilet", "shelf"], "question": "select the stool that is in the center of the toilet and the shelf. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 37, 57], "object_names": ["carpet", "toilet", "shelf"], "question": "find the carpet that is in the middle of the toilet and the shelf. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 37, 67], "object_names": ["table", "toilet", "case"], "question": "choose the table that is in the middle of the toilet and the case. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["vertically on a beige carpet"], "object_ids": [35, 38, 57], "object_names": ["table", "bed", "shelf"], "question": "find the table that is in the middle of the bed and the shelf. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 38, 68], "object_names": ["stand", "bed", "chair"], "question": "choose the stand that is between the bed and the chair. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 38, 98], "object_names": ["stand", "bed", "computer"], "question": "find the stand that is between the bed and the computer. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 46, 48], "object_names": ["towel", "oven", "guitar"], "question": "choose the towel that is in the center of the oven and the guitar. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 46, 49], "object_names": ["towel", "oven", "tissue box"], "question": "the towel that is in the middle of the oven and the tissue. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 46, 68], "object_names": ["towel", "oven", "chair"], "question": "select the towel that is in the center of the oven and the chair. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table"], "object_ids": [35, 47, 57], "object_names": ["table", "basket", "shelf"], "question": "choose the table that is in the middle of the basket and the shelf. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35, 48, 57], "object_names": ["table", "guitar", "shelf"], "question": "the table that is in the middle of the guitar and the shelf. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 48, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the middle of the guitar and the bicycle. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 48, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar", "chair"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the middle of the guitar and the chair. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 48, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar", "lamp"], "question": "select the backpack that is in the center of the guitar and the lamp. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 53, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave", "mirror"], "question": "the doorframe that is in the center of the microwave and the mirror. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 55, 57], "object_names": ["towel", "door", "shelf"], "question": "the towel that is in the center of the door and the shelf. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 55, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "door", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the center of the door and the bicycle. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 55, 67], "object_names": ["towel", "door", "case"], "question": "choose the towel that is in the center of the door and the case. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [35, 57, 58], "object_names": ["table", "shelf", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the table that is between the shelf and the bicycle. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [35, 57, 68], "object_names": ["table", "shelf", "chair"], "question": "the table that is in the center of the shelf and the chair. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 57, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "shelf", "chair"], "question": "choose the backpack that is in the middle of the shelf and the chair. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["velvet", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [35, 58, 67], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle", "case"], "question": "select the table that is in the center of the bicycle and the case. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35, 67, 189], "object_names": ["table", "case", "lamp"], "question": "choose the table that is in the middle of the case and the lamp. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3, 4], "object_names": ["table", "counter"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the counter. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 4], "object_names": ["table", "counter"], "question": "select the table that is close to the counter. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 4], "object_names": ["table", "counter"], "question": "select the table that is near the counter. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36, 4], "object_names": ["table", "counter"], "question": "choose the table that is farthest from the counter. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36, 4], "object_names": ["table", "counter"], "question": "choose the table that is far from the counter. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 4], "object_names": ["table", "counter"], "question": "choose the table that is far away from the counter. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 4], "object_names": ["curtain", "counter"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the counter. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 4], "object_names": ["curtain", "counter"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the counter. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 4], "object_names": ["curtain", "counter"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the counter. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 4], "object_names": ["curtain", "counter"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the counter. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 4], "object_names": ["curtain", "counter"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the counter. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 4], "object_names": ["curtain", "counter"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the counter. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15, 4], "object_names": ["bin", "counter"], "question": "select the bin that is farthest from the counter. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 4], "object_names": ["bin", "counter"], "question": "select the bin that is far from the counter. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 4], "object_names": ["bin", "counter"], "question": "select the bin that is far away from the counter. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 4], "object_names": ["backpack", "counter"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the counter. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 4], "object_names": ["backpack", "counter"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the counter. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 4], "object_names": ["backpack", "counter"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the counter. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 4], "object_names": ["backpack", "counter"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the counter. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 4], "object_names": ["backpack", "counter"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the counter. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 4], "object_names": ["backpack", "counter"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the counter. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["stool", "counter"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the counter. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["stool", "counter"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the counter. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 4], "object_names": ["stool", "counter"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the counter. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 4], "object_names": ["stand", "counter"], "question": "select the stand that is farthest from the counter. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 4], "object_names": ["stand", "counter"], "question": "select the stand that is far from the counter. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 4], "object_names": ["stand", "counter"], "question": "select the stand that is far away from the counter. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "select the doorframe that is closer to the counter. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "select the doorframe that is close to the counter. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 4], "object_names": ["doorframe", "counter"], "question": "select the doorframe that is near the counter. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 4], "object_names": ["cup", "counter"], "question": "find the cup that is farthest from the counter. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 4], "object_names": ["cup", "counter"], "question": "find the cup that is far from the counter. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 4], "object_names": ["cup", "counter"], "question": "find the cup that is far away from the counter. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 4], "object_names": ["carpet", "counter"], "question": "select the carpet that is closer to the counter. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 4], "object_names": ["carpet", "counter"], "question": "select the carpet that is close to the counter. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 4], "object_names": ["carpet", "counter"], "question": "select the carpet that is near the counter. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 4], "object_names": ["picture", "counter"], "question": "find the picture that is closer to the counter. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 4], "object_names": ["picture", "counter"], "question": "find the picture that is close to the counter. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 4], "object_names": ["picture", "counter"], "question": "find the picture that is near the counter. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 4], "object_names": ["towel", "counter"], "question": "find the towel that is closer to the counter. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 4], "object_names": ["towel", "counter"], "question": "find the towel that is close to the counter. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 4], "object_names": ["towel", "counter"], "question": "find the towel that is near the counter. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 4], "object_names": ["towel", "counter"], "question": "select the towel that is farthest from the counter. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 4], "object_names": ["towel", "counter"], "question": "select the towel that is far from the counter. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 4], "object_names": ["towel", "counter"], "question": "select the towel that is far away from the counter. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 5], "object_names": ["table", "shower"], "question": "find the table that is closer to the shower. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 5], "object_names": ["table", "shower"], "question": "find the table that is close to the shower. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36, 5], "object_names": ["table", "shower"], "question": "find the table that is near the shower. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["soft and velvety"], "object_ids": [35, 5], "object_names": ["table", "shower"], "question": "find the table that is farthest from the shower. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [35, 5], "object_names": ["table", "shower"], "question": "find the table that is far from the shower. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["soft and velvety"], "object_ids": [35, 5], "object_names": ["table", "shower"], "question": "find the table that is far away from the shower. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 5], "object_names": ["curtain", "shower"], "question": "choose the curtain that is closer to the shower. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 5], "object_names": ["curtain", "shower"], "question": "choose the curtain that is close to the shower. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 5], "object_names": ["curtain", "shower"], "question": "choose the curtain that is near the shower. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 5], "object_names": ["curtain", "shower"], "question": "select the curtain that is farthest from the shower. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 5], "object_names": ["curtain", "shower"], "question": "select the curtain that is far from the shower. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 5], "object_names": ["curtain", "shower"], "question": "select the curtain that is far away from the shower. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 5], "object_names": ["bin", "shower"], "question": "find the bin that is closer to the shower. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 5], "object_names": ["bin", "shower"], "question": "find the bin that is close to the shower. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 5], "object_names": ["bin", "shower"], "question": "find the bin that is near the shower. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 5], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the shower. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 5], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the shower. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 5], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower"], "question": "the backpack that is near the shower. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 5], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the shower. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 5], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the shower. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 5], "object_names": ["backpack", "shower"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the shower. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 5], "object_names": ["stool", "shower"], "question": "the stool that is closer to the shower. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 5], "object_names": ["stool", "shower"], "question": "the stool that is close to the shower. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 5], "object_names": ["stool", "shower"], "question": "the stool that is near the shower. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 5], "object_names": ["stool", "shower"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the shower. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 5], "object_names": ["stool", "shower"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the shower. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 5], "object_names": ["stool", "shower"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the shower. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 5], "object_names": ["stand", "shower"], "question": "find the stand that is farthest from the shower. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 5], "object_names": ["stand", "shower"], "question": "find the stand that is far from the shower. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 5], "object_names": ["stand", "shower"], "question": "find the stand that is far away from the shower. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 5], "object_names": ["doorframe", "shower"], "question": "the doorframe that is farthest from the shower. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 5], "object_names": ["doorframe", "shower"], "question": "the doorframe that is far from the shower. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 5], "object_names": ["doorframe", "shower"], "question": "the doorframe that is far away from the shower. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 5], "object_names": ["cup", "shower"], "question": "find the cup that is closer to the shower. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 5], "object_names": ["cup", "shower"], "question": "find the cup that is close to the shower. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 5], "object_names": ["cup", "shower"], "question": "find the cup that is near the shower. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 5], "object_names": ["carpet", "shower"], "question": "find the carpet that is beside the shower. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 5], "object_names": ["carpet", "shower"], "question": "find the carpet that is beside the shower. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 5], "object_names": ["carpet", "shower"], "question": "find the carpet that is beside the shower. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 5], "object_names": ["picture", "shower"], "question": "select the picture that is closer to the shower. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 5], "object_names": ["picture", "shower"], "question": "select the picture that is close to the shower. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 5], "object_names": ["picture", "shower"], "question": "select the picture that is near the shower. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 5], "object_names": ["towel", "shower"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the shower. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 5], "object_names": ["towel", "shower"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the shower. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 5], "object_names": ["towel", "shower"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the shower. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 8], "object_names": ["table", "desk"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the desk. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 8], "object_names": ["table", "desk"], "question": "select the table that is close to the desk. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 8], "object_names": ["table", "desk"], "question": "select the table that is near the desk. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 8], "object_names": ["table", "desk"], "question": "find the table that is farthest from the desk. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 8], "object_names": ["table", "desk"], "question": "find the table that is far from the desk. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 8], "object_names": ["table", "desk"], "question": "find the table that is far away from the desk. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the desk. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the desk. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the desk. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the desk. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the desk. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 8], "object_names": ["curtain", "desk"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the desk. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 8], "object_names": ["bin", "desk"], "question": "select the bin that is closer to the desk. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 8], "object_names": ["bin", "desk"], "question": "select the bin that is close to the desk. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 8], "object_names": ["bin", "desk"], "question": "select the bin that is near the desk. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 8], "object_names": ["backpack", "desk"], "question": "choose the backpack that is closer to the desk. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63, 8], "object_names": ["backpack", "desk"], "question": "choose the backpack that is close to the desk. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 8], "object_names": ["backpack", "desk"], "question": "choose the backpack that is near the desk. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 8], "object_names": ["backpack", "desk"], "question": "the backpack that is farthest from the desk. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 8], "object_names": ["backpack", "desk"], "question": "the backpack that is far from the desk. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 8], "object_names": ["backpack", "desk"], "question": "the backpack that is far away from the desk. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 8], "object_names": ["stool", "desk"], "question": "the stool that is closer to the desk. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 8], "object_names": ["stool", "desk"], "question": "the stool that is close to the desk. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 8], "object_names": ["stool", "desk"], "question": "the stool that is near the desk. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 8], "object_names": ["stool", "desk"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the desk. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 8], "object_names": ["stool", "desk"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the desk. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 8], "object_names": ["stool", "desk"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the desk. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 8], "object_names": ["stand", "desk"], "question": "select the stand that is closer to the desk. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 8], "object_names": ["stand", "desk"], "question": "select the stand that is close to the desk. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 8], "object_names": ["stand", "desk"], "question": "select the stand that is near the desk. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 8], "object_names": ["doorframe", "desk"], "question": "select the doorframe that is farthest from the desk. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 8], "object_names": ["doorframe", "desk"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far from the desk. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 8], "object_names": ["doorframe", "desk"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far away from the desk. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 8], "object_names": ["cup", "desk"], "question": "select the cup that is closer to the desk. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 8], "object_names": ["cup", "desk"], "question": "select the cup that is close to the desk. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 8], "object_names": ["cup", "desk"], "question": "select the cup that is near the desk. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage"], "object_ids": [150, 8], "object_names": ["carpet", "desk"], "question": "select the carpet that is farthest from the desk. What is state of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 8], "object_names": ["carpet", "desk"], "question": "select the carpet that is far from the desk. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 8], "object_names": ["carpet", "desk"], "question": "select the carpet that is far away from the desk. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "the picture that is farthest from the desk. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "the picture that is far from the desk. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 8], "object_names": ["picture", "desk"], "question": "the picture that is far away from the desk. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 8], "object_names": ["towel", "desk"], "question": "the towel that is farthest from the desk. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 8], "object_names": ["towel", "desk"], "question": "the towel that is far from the desk. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 8], "object_names": ["towel", "desk"], "question": "the towel that is far away from the desk. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 11], "object_names": ["table", "sink"], "question": "find the table that is closer to the sink. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 11], "object_names": ["table", "sink"], "question": "find the table that is close to the sink. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 11], "object_names": ["table", "sink"], "question": "find the table that is near the sink. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 11], "object_names": ["table", "sink"], "question": "find the table that is farthest from the sink. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 11], "object_names": ["table", "sink"], "question": "find the table that is far from the sink. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 11], "object_names": ["table", "sink"], "question": "find the table that is far away from the sink. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 11], "object_names": ["curtain", "sink"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the sink. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 11], "object_names": ["curtain", "sink"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the sink. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 11], "object_names": ["curtain", "sink"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the sink. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 11], "object_names": ["curtain", "sink"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the sink. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 11], "object_names": ["curtain", "sink"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the sink. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 11], "object_names": ["curtain", "sink"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the sink. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 11], "object_names": ["bin", "sink"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the sink. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 11], "object_names": ["bin", "sink"], "question": "the bin that is far from the sink. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 11], "object_names": ["bin", "sink"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the sink. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 11], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the sink. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 11], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the sink. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 11], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the sink. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 11], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink"], "question": "select the backpack that is farthest from the sink. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 11], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink"], "question": "select the backpack that is far from the sink. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 11], "object_names": ["backpack", "sink"], "question": "select the backpack that is far away from the sink. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 11], "object_names": ["stool", "sink"], "question": "choose the stool that is closer to the sink. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 11], "object_names": ["stool", "sink"], "question": "choose the stool that is close to the sink. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 11], "object_names": ["stool", "sink"], "question": "choose the stool that is near the sink. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 11], "object_names": ["stool", "sink"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the sink. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 11], "object_names": ["stool", "sink"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the sink. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 11], "object_names": ["stool", "sink"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the sink. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 11], "object_names": ["stand", "sink"], "question": "choose the stand that is farthest from the sink. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 11], "object_names": ["stand", "sink"], "question": "choose the stand that is far from the sink. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 11], "object_names": ["stand", "sink"], "question": "choose the stand that is far away from the sink. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is farthest from the sink. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is far from the sink. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 11], "object_names": ["doorframe", "sink"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is far away from the sink. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 11], "object_names": ["cup", "sink"], "question": "select the cup that is closer to the sink. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 11], "object_names": ["cup", "sink"], "question": "select the cup that is close to the sink. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 11], "object_names": ["cup", "sink"], "question": "select the cup that is near the sink. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 11], "object_names": ["carpet", "sink"], "question": "the carpet that is closer to the sink. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 11], "object_names": ["carpet", "sink"], "question": "the carpet that is close to the sink. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 11], "object_names": ["carpet", "sink"], "question": "the carpet that is near the sink. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 11], "object_names": ["picture", "sink"], "question": "select the picture that is closer to the sink. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 11], "object_names": ["picture", "sink"], "question": "select the picture that is close to the sink. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 11], "object_names": ["picture", "sink"], "question": "select the picture that is near the sink. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168, 11], "object_names": ["towel", "sink"], "question": "select the towel that is closer to the sink. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 11], "object_names": ["towel", "sink"], "question": "select the towel that is close to the sink. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 11], "object_names": ["towel", "sink"], "question": "select the towel that is near the sink. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 11], "object_names": ["towel", "sink"], "question": "select the towel that is farthest from the sink. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 11], "object_names": ["towel", "sink"], "question": "select the towel that is far from the sink. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 11], "object_names": ["towel", "sink"], "question": "select the towel that is far away from the sink. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 12], "object_names": ["table", "scale"], "question": "the table that is closer to the scale. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 12], "object_names": ["table", "scale"], "question": "the table that is close to the scale. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 12], "object_names": ["table", "scale"], "question": "the table that is near the scale. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 12], "object_names": ["curtain", "scale"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the scale. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 12], "object_names": ["curtain", "scale"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the scale. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 12], "object_names": ["curtain", "scale"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the scale. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 12], "object_names": ["curtain", "scale"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the scale. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 12], "object_names": ["curtain", "scale"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the scale. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 12], "object_names": ["curtain", "scale"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the scale. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 12], "object_names": ["backpack", "scale"], "question": "select the backpack that is closer to the scale. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 12], "object_names": ["backpack", "scale"], "question": "select the backpack that is close to the scale. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 12], "object_names": ["backpack", "scale"], "question": "select the backpack that is near the scale. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 12], "object_names": ["backpack", "scale"], "question": "the backpack that is farthest from the scale. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 12], "object_names": ["backpack", "scale"], "question": "the backpack that is far from the scale. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 12], "object_names": ["backpack", "scale"], "question": "the backpack that is far away from the scale. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 12], "object_names": ["stool", "scale"], "question": "find the stool that is closer to the scale. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 12], "object_names": ["stool", "scale"], "question": "find the stool that is close to the scale. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 12], "object_names": ["stool", "scale"], "question": "find the stool that is near the scale. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 12], "object_names": ["stool", "scale"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the scale. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 12], "object_names": ["stool", "scale"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the scale. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 12], "object_names": ["stool", "scale"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the scale. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 12], "object_names": ["stand", "scale"], "question": "select the stand that is farthest from the scale. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 12], "object_names": ["stand", "scale"], "question": "select the stand that is far from the scale. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 12], "object_names": ["stand", "scale"], "question": "select the stand that is far away from the scale. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is farthest from the scale. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is far from the scale. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 12], "object_names": ["doorframe", "scale"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is far away from the scale. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 12], "object_names": ["cup", "scale"], "question": "choose the cup that is closer to the scale. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 12], "object_names": ["cup", "scale"], "question": "choose the cup that is close to the scale. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 12], "object_names": ["cup", "scale"], "question": "choose the cup that is near the scale. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage"], "object_ids": [150, 12], "object_names": ["carpet", "scale"], "question": "select the carpet that is closer to the scale. What is state of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 12], "object_names": ["carpet", "scale"], "question": "select the carpet that is close to the scale. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 12], "object_names": ["carpet", "scale"], "question": "select the carpet that is near the scale. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "find the picture that is closer to the scale. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "find the picture that is close to the scale. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 12], "object_names": ["picture", "scale"], "question": "find the picture that is near the scale. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 12], "object_names": ["towel", "scale"], "question": "choose the towel that is farthest from the scale. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 12], "object_names": ["towel", "scale"], "question": "choose the towel that is far from the scale. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 12], "object_names": ["towel", "scale"], "question": "choose the towel that is far away from the scale. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35, 16], "object_names": ["table", "tv"], "question": "choose the table that is closer to the tv. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["vertically on a beige carpet"], "object_ids": [35, 16], "object_names": ["table", "tv"], "question": "choose the table that is close to the tv. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [35, 16], "object_names": ["table", "tv"], "question": "choose the table that is near the tv. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 16], "object_names": ["table", "tv"], "question": "select the table that is farthest from the tv. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36, 16], "object_names": ["table", "tv"], "question": "select the table that is far from the tv. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 16], "object_names": ["table", "tv"], "question": "select the table that is far away from the tv. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 16], "object_names": ["curtain", "tv"], "question": "choose the curtain that is closer to the tv. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 16], "object_names": ["curtain", "tv"], "question": "choose the curtain that is close to the tv. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 16], "object_names": ["curtain", "tv"], "question": "choose the curtain that is near the tv. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 16], "object_names": ["curtain", "tv"], "question": "select the curtain that is farthest from the tv. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 16], "object_names": ["curtain", "tv"], "question": "select the curtain that is far from the tv. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 16], "object_names": ["curtain", "tv"], "question": "select the curtain that is far away from the tv. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15, 16], "object_names": ["bin", "tv"], "question": "select the bin that is closer to the tv. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 16], "object_names": ["bin", "tv"], "question": "select the bin that is close to the tv. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15, 16], "object_names": ["bin", "tv"], "question": "select the bin that is near the tv. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 16], "object_names": ["bin", "tv"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the tv. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 16], "object_names": ["bin", "tv"], "question": "the bin that is far from the tv. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14, 16], "object_names": ["bin", "tv"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the tv. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 16], "object_names": ["backpack", "tv"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the tv. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 16], "object_names": ["backpack", "tv"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the tv. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 16], "object_names": ["backpack", "tv"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the tv. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 16], "object_names": ["backpack", "tv"], "question": "the backpack that is farthest from the tv. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 16], "object_names": ["backpack", "tv"], "question": "the backpack that is far from the tv. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 16], "object_names": ["backpack", "tv"], "question": "the backpack that is far away from the tv. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 16], "object_names": ["stand", "tv"], "question": "the stand that is closer to the tv. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 16], "object_names": ["stand", "tv"], "question": "the stand that is close to the tv. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 16], "object_names": ["stand", "tv"], "question": "the stand that is near the tv. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rounded toe", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59, 16], "object_names": ["shoe", "tv"], "question": "choose the shoe that is closer to the tv. What is shape of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [59, 16], "object_names": ["shoe", "tv"], "question": "choose the shoe that is close to the tv. What is color of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["rounded toe", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59, 16], "object_names": ["shoe", "tv"], "question": "choose the shoe that is near the tv. What is shape of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [162, 16], "object_names": ["shoe", "tv"], "question": "the shoe that is farthest from the tv. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["flat on the floor"], "object_ids": [162, 16], "object_names": ["shoe", "tv"], "question": "the shoe that is far from the tv. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["black and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [162, 16], "object_names": ["shoe", "tv"], "question": "the shoe that is far away from the tv. What is color of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 16], "object_names": ["doorframe", "tv"], "question": "find the doorframe that is farthest from the tv. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 16], "object_names": ["doorframe", "tv"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far from the tv. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 16], "object_names": ["doorframe", "tv"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far away from the tv. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 16], "object_names": ["cup", "tv"], "question": "select the cup that is farthest from the tv. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 16], "object_names": ["cup", "tv"], "question": "select the cup that is far from the tv. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 16], "object_names": ["cup", "tv"], "question": "select the cup that is far away from the tv. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 16], "object_names": ["carpet", "tv"], "question": "choose the carpet that is farthest from the tv. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 16], "object_names": ["carpet", "tv"], "question": "choose the carpet that is far from the tv. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 16], "object_names": ["carpet", "tv"], "question": "choose the carpet that is far away from the tv. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 16], "object_names": ["towel", "tv"], "question": "choose the towel that is closer to the tv. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 16], "object_names": ["towel", "tv"], "question": "choose the towel that is close to the tv. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 16], "object_names": ["towel", "tv"], "question": "choose the towel that is near the tv. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 16], "object_names": ["towel", "tv"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the tv. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 16], "object_names": ["towel", "tv"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the tv. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 16], "object_names": ["towel", "tv"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the tv. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 18], "object_names": ["table", "clock"], "question": "choose the table that is closer to the clock. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36, 18], "object_names": ["table", "clock"], "question": "choose the table that is close to the clock. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 18], "object_names": ["table", "clock"], "question": "choose the table that is near the clock. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 18], "object_names": ["table", "clock"], "question": "choose the table that is farthest from the clock. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 18], "object_names": ["table", "clock"], "question": "choose the table that is far from the clock. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 18], "object_names": ["table", "clock"], "question": "choose the table that is far away from the clock. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the clock. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the clock. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the clock. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "choose the curtain that is farthest from the clock. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far from the clock. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 18], "object_names": ["curtain", "clock"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far away from the clock. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 18], "object_names": ["bin", "clock"], "question": "choose the bin that is closer to the clock. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 18], "object_names": ["bin", "clock"], "question": "choose the bin that is close to the clock. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15, 18], "object_names": ["bin", "clock"], "question": "choose the bin that is near the clock. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 18], "object_names": ["bin", "clock"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the clock. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 18], "object_names": ["bin", "clock"], "question": "the bin that is far from the clock. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["serving as a container for rubbish"], "object_ids": [14, 18], "object_names": ["bin", "clock"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the clock. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 18], "object_names": ["backpack", "clock"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the clock. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 18], "object_names": ["backpack", "clock"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the clock. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63, 18], "object_names": ["backpack", "clock"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the clock. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 18], "object_names": ["backpack", "clock"], "question": "find the backpack that is farthest from the clock. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 18], "object_names": ["backpack", "clock"], "question": "find the backpack that is far from the clock. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 18], "object_names": ["backpack", "clock"], "question": "find the backpack that is far away from the clock. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 18], "object_names": ["stool", "clock"], "question": "the stool that is closer to the clock. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 18], "object_names": ["stool", "clock"], "question": "the stool that is close to the clock. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 18], "object_names": ["stool", "clock"], "question": "the stool that is near the clock. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 18], "object_names": ["stool", "clock"], "question": "the stool that is farthest from the clock. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 18], "object_names": ["stool", "clock"], "question": "the stool that is far from the clock. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 18], "object_names": ["stool", "clock"], "question": "the stool that is far away from the clock. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 18], "object_names": ["stand", "clock"], "question": "select the stand that is closer to the clock. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 18], "object_names": ["stand", "clock"], "question": "select the stand that is close to the clock. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 18], "object_names": ["stand", "clock"], "question": "select the stand that is near the clock. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["providing comfort and support for walking or running"], "object_ids": [162, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "choose the shoe that is closer to the clock. What is function of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["good condition, showing no signs of wear or damage"], "object_ids": [162, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "choose the shoe that is close to the clock. What is state of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["providing comfort and support for walking or running"], "object_ids": [162, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "choose the shoe that is near the clock. What is function of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "choose the shoe that is farthest from the clock. What is color of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "choose the shoe that is far from the clock. What is size of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["rounded toe", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59, 18], "object_names": ["shoe", "clock"], "question": "choose the shoe that is far away from the clock. What is shape of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 18], "object_names": ["doorframe", "clock"], "question": "select the doorframe that is farthest from the clock. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 18], "object_names": ["doorframe", "clock"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far from the clock. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 18], "object_names": ["doorframe", "clock"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far away from the clock. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 18], "object_names": ["cup", "clock"], "question": "choose the cup that is closer to the clock. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 18], "object_names": ["cup", "clock"], "question": "choose the cup that is close to the clock. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 18], "object_names": ["cup", "clock"], "question": "choose the cup that is near the clock. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage"], "object_ids": [150, 18], "object_names": ["carpet", "clock"], "question": "find the carpet that is farthest from the clock. What is state of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 18], "object_names": ["carpet", "clock"], "question": "find the carpet that is far from the clock. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 18], "object_names": ["carpet", "clock"], "question": "find the carpet that is far away from the clock. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 18], "object_names": ["picture", "clock"], "question": "choose the picture that is farthest from the clock. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 18], "object_names": ["picture", "clock"], "question": "choose the picture that is far from the clock. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 18], "object_names": ["picture", "clock"], "question": "choose the picture that is far away from the clock. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table"], "object_ids": [35, 33], "object_names": ["table", "couch"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the couch. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [35, 33], "object_names": ["table", "couch"], "question": "select the table that is close to the couch. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35, 33], "object_names": ["table", "couch"], "question": "select the table that is near the couch. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36, 33], "object_names": ["table", "couch"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the couch. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 33], "object_names": ["table", "couch"], "question": "the table that is far from the couch. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 33], "object_names": ["table", "couch"], "question": "the table that is far away from the couch. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 33], "object_names": ["curtain", "couch"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the couch. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 33], "object_names": ["curtain", "couch"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the couch. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 33], "object_names": ["curtain", "couch"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the couch. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 33], "object_names": ["curtain", "couch"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the couch. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 33], "object_names": ["curtain", "couch"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the couch. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 33], "object_names": ["curtain", "couch"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the couch. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [13, 33], "object_names": ["bin", "couch"], "question": "choose the bin that is closer to the couch. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [13, 33], "object_names": ["bin", "couch"], "question": "choose the bin that is close to the couch. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [13, 33], "object_names": ["bin", "couch"], "question": "choose the bin that is near the couch. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 33], "object_names": ["bin", "couch"], "question": "choose the bin that is farthest from the couch. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15, 33], "object_names": ["bin", "couch"], "question": "choose the bin that is far from the couch. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 33], "object_names": ["bin", "couch"], "question": "choose the bin that is far away from the couch. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is closer to the couch. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is close to the couch. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is near the couch. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the couch. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the couch. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 33], "object_names": ["backpack", "couch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the couch. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the couch. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the couch. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 33], "object_names": ["stool", "couch"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the couch. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 33], "object_names": ["cup", "couch"], "question": "the cup that is farthest from the couch. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 33], "object_names": ["cup", "couch"], "question": "the cup that is far from the couch. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 33], "object_names": ["cup", "couch"], "question": "the cup that is far away from the couch. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 33], "object_names": ["carpet", "couch"], "question": "select the carpet that is farthest from the couch. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 33], "object_names": ["carpet", "couch"], "question": "select the carpet that is far from the couch. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 33], "object_names": ["carpet", "couch"], "question": "select the carpet that is far away from the couch. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "the towel that is closer to the couch. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "the towel that is close to the couch. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "the towel that is near the couch. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the couch. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the couch. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168, 33], "object_names": ["towel", "couch"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the couch. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 34], "object_names": ["table", "refrigerator"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the refrigerator. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 34], "object_names": ["table", "refrigerator"], "question": "select the table that is close to the refrigerator. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 34], "object_names": ["table", "refrigerator"], "question": "select the table that is near the refrigerator. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 34], "object_names": ["table", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the table that is farthest from the refrigerator. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 34], "object_names": ["table", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the table that is far from the refrigerator. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 34], "object_names": ["table", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the table that is far away from the refrigerator. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 34], "object_names": ["curtain", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the curtain that is closer to the refrigerator. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 34], "object_names": ["curtain", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the curtain that is close to the refrigerator. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 34], "object_names": ["curtain", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the curtain that is near the refrigerator. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 34], "object_names": ["curtain", "refrigerator"], "question": "select the curtain that is farthest from the refrigerator. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 34], "object_names": ["curtain", "refrigerator"], "question": "select the curtain that is far from the refrigerator. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 34], "object_names": ["curtain", "refrigerator"], "question": "select the curtain that is far away from the refrigerator. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the bin that is farthest from the refrigerator. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the bin that is far from the refrigerator. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 34], "object_names": ["bin", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the bin that is far away from the refrigerator. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 34], "object_names": ["stool", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the refrigerator. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 34], "object_names": ["stool", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the refrigerator. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 34], "object_names": ["stool", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the refrigerator. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 34], "object_names": ["stand", "refrigerator"], "question": "the stand that is farthest from the refrigerator. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 34], "object_names": ["stand", "refrigerator"], "question": "the stand that is far from the refrigerator. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 34], "object_names": ["stand", "refrigerator"], "question": "the stand that is far away from the refrigerator. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 34], "object_names": ["doorframe", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the doorframe that is closer to the refrigerator. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 34], "object_names": ["doorframe", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the doorframe that is close to the refrigerator. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 34], "object_names": ["doorframe", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the doorframe that is near the refrigerator. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the cup that is farthest from the refrigerator. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the cup that is far from the refrigerator. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 34], "object_names": ["cup", "refrigerator"], "question": "choose the cup that is far away from the refrigerator. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 34], "object_names": ["carpet", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the carpet that is closer to the refrigerator. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 34], "object_names": ["carpet", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the carpet that is close to the refrigerator. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 34], "object_names": ["carpet", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the carpet that is near the refrigerator. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 34], "object_names": ["picture", "refrigerator"], "question": "the picture that is closer to the refrigerator. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 34], "object_names": ["picture", "refrigerator"], "question": "the picture that is close to the refrigerator. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 34], "object_names": ["picture", "refrigerator"], "question": "the picture that is near the refrigerator. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 34], "object_names": ["towel", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the towel that is closer to the refrigerator. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 34], "object_names": ["towel", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the towel that is close to the refrigerator. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 34], "object_names": ["towel", "refrigerator"], "question": "find the towel that is near the refrigerator. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 34], "object_names": ["towel", "refrigerator"], "question": "the towel that is farthest from the refrigerator. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [168, 34], "object_names": ["towel", "refrigerator"], "question": "the towel that is far from the refrigerator. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 34], "object_names": ["towel", "refrigerator"], "question": "the towel that is far away from the refrigerator. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 37], "object_names": ["table", "toilet"], "question": "the table that is closer to the toilet. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 37], "object_names": ["table", "toilet"], "question": "the table that is close to the toilet. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3, 37], "object_names": ["table", "toilet"], "question": "the table that is near the toilet. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table"], "object_ids": [35, 37], "object_names": ["table", "toilet"], "question": "find the table that is farthest from the toilet. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["soft and velvety"], "object_ids": [35, 37], "object_names": ["table", "toilet"], "question": "find the table that is far from the toilet. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [35, 37], "object_names": ["table", "toilet"], "question": "find the table that is far away from the toilet. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 37], "object_names": ["curtain", "toilet"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the toilet. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 37], "object_names": ["curtain", "toilet"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the toilet. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 37], "object_names": ["curtain", "toilet"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the toilet. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 37], "object_names": ["curtain", "toilet"], "question": "the curtain that is farthest from the toilet. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 37], "object_names": ["curtain", "toilet"], "question": "the curtain that is far from the toilet. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 37], "object_names": ["curtain", "toilet"], "question": "the curtain that is far away from the toilet. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 37], "object_names": ["bin", "toilet"], "question": "select the bin that is farthest from the toilet. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 37], "object_names": ["bin", "toilet"], "question": "select the bin that is far from the toilet. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15, 37], "object_names": ["bin", "toilet"], "question": "select the bin that is far away from the toilet. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 37], "object_names": ["backpack", "toilet"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the toilet. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 37], "object_names": ["backpack", "toilet"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the toilet. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 37], "object_names": ["backpack", "toilet"], "question": "the backpack that is near the toilet. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 37], "object_names": ["backpack", "toilet"], "question": "select the backpack that is farthest from the toilet. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 37], "object_names": ["backpack", "toilet"], "question": "select the backpack that is far from the toilet. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 37], "object_names": ["backpack", "toilet"], "question": "select the backpack that is far away from the toilet. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 37], "object_names": ["stool", "toilet"], "question": "choose the stool that is closer to the toilet. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 37], "object_names": ["stool", "toilet"], "question": "choose the stool that is close to the toilet. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 37], "object_names": ["stool", "toilet"], "question": "choose the stool that is near the toilet. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 37], "object_names": ["stool", "toilet"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the toilet. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 37], "object_names": ["stool", "toilet"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the toilet. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 37], "object_names": ["stool", "toilet"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the toilet. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 37], "object_names": ["stand", "toilet"], "question": "select the stand that is farthest from the toilet. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 37], "object_names": ["stand", "toilet"], "question": "select the stand that is far from the toilet. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 37], "object_names": ["stand", "toilet"], "question": "select the stand that is far away from the toilet. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "find the doorframe that is farthest from the toilet. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far from the toilet. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 37], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toilet"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far away from the toilet. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 37], "object_names": ["cup", "toilet"], "question": "the cup that is closer to the toilet. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 37], "object_names": ["cup", "toilet"], "question": "the cup that is close to the toilet. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 37], "object_names": ["cup", "toilet"], "question": "the cup that is near the toilet. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 37], "object_names": ["carpet", "toilet"], "question": "the carpet that is beside the toilet. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 37], "object_names": ["carpet", "toilet"], "question": "the carpet that is beside the toilet. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 37], "object_names": ["carpet", "toilet"], "question": "the carpet that is beside the toilet. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 37], "object_names": ["picture", "toilet"], "question": "the picture that is closer to the toilet. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 37], "object_names": ["picture", "toilet"], "question": "the picture that is close to the toilet. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 37], "object_names": ["picture", "toilet"], "question": "the picture that is near the toilet. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 37], "object_names": ["towel", "toilet"], "question": "find the towel that is beside the toilet. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 37], "object_names": ["towel", "toilet"], "question": "find the towel that is beside the toilet. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 37], "object_names": ["towel", "toilet"], "question": "find the towel that is beside the toilet. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 37], "object_names": ["towel", "toilet"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the toilet. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 37], "object_names": ["towel", "toilet"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the toilet. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 37], "object_names": ["towel", "toilet"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the toilet. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "find the table that is closer to the bed. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "find the table that is close to the bed. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "find the table that is near the bed. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "select the table that is farthest from the bed. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "select the table that is far from the bed. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 38], "object_names": ["table", "bed"], "question": "select the table that is far away from the bed. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 38], "object_names": ["curtain", "bed"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the bed. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 38], "object_names": ["curtain", "bed"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the bed. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 38], "object_names": ["curtain", "bed"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the bed. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 38], "object_names": ["curtain", "bed"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the bed. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 38], "object_names": ["curtain", "bed"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the bed. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 38], "object_names": ["curtain", "bed"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the bed. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 38], "object_names": ["bin", "bed"], "question": "the bin that is closer to the bed. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 38], "object_names": ["bin", "bed"], "question": "the bin that is close to the bed. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 38], "object_names": ["bin", "bed"], "question": "the bin that is near the bed. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "select the backpack that is closer to the bed. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "select the backpack that is close to the bed. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "select the backpack that is near the bed. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "select the backpack that is farthest from the bed. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "select the backpack that is far from the bed. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 38], "object_names": ["backpack", "bed"], "question": "select the backpack that is far away from the bed. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 38], "object_names": ["stool", "bed"], "question": "the stool that is closer to the bed. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 38], "object_names": ["stool", "bed"], "question": "the stool that is close to the bed. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 38], "object_names": ["stool", "bed"], "question": "the stool that is near the bed. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 38], "object_names": ["stool", "bed"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the bed. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 38], "object_names": ["stool", "bed"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the bed. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 38], "object_names": ["stool", "bed"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the bed. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 38], "object_names": ["doorframe", "bed"], "question": "find the doorframe that is farthest from the bed. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 38], "object_names": ["doorframe", "bed"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far from the bed. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 38], "object_names": ["doorframe", "bed"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far away from the bed. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "the cup that is closer to the bed. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "the cup that is close to the bed. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 38], "object_names": ["cup", "bed"], "question": "the cup that is near the bed. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 38], "object_names": ["carpet", "bed"], "question": "select the carpet that is farthest from the bed. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 38], "object_names": ["carpet", "bed"], "question": "select the carpet that is far from the bed. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 38], "object_names": ["carpet", "bed"], "question": "select the carpet that is far away from the bed. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the bed. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the bed. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 38], "object_names": ["towel", "bed"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the bed. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 46], "object_names": ["table", "oven"], "question": "the table that is closer to the oven. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 46], "object_names": ["table", "oven"], "question": "the table that is close to the oven. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 46], "object_names": ["table", "oven"], "question": "the table that is near the oven. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 46], "object_names": ["table", "oven"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the oven. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 46], "object_names": ["table", "oven"], "question": "the table that is far from the oven. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 46], "object_names": ["table", "oven"], "question": "the table that is far away from the oven. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 46], "object_names": ["curtain", "oven"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the oven. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 46], "object_names": ["curtain", "oven"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the oven. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 46], "object_names": ["curtain", "oven"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the oven. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 46], "object_names": ["curtain", "oven"], "question": "the curtain that is farthest from the oven. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 46], "object_names": ["curtain", "oven"], "question": "the curtain that is far from the oven. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 46], "object_names": ["curtain", "oven"], "question": "the curtain that is far away from the oven. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the oven. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "the bin that is far from the oven. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 46], "object_names": ["bin", "oven"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the oven. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 46], "object_names": ["backpack", "oven"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the oven. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 46], "object_names": ["backpack", "oven"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the oven. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 46], "object_names": ["backpack", "oven"], "question": "the backpack that is near the oven. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 46], "object_names": ["backpack", "oven"], "question": "the backpack that is farthest from the oven. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 46], "object_names": ["backpack", "oven"], "question": "the backpack that is far from the oven. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 46], "object_names": ["backpack", "oven"], "question": "the backpack that is far away from the oven. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 46], "object_names": ["stool", "oven"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the oven. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 46], "object_names": ["stool", "oven"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the oven. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 46], "object_names": ["stool", "oven"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the oven. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 46], "object_names": ["stand", "oven"], "question": "choose the stand that is farthest from the oven. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 46], "object_names": ["stand", "oven"], "question": "choose the stand that is far from the oven. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 46], "object_names": ["stand", "oven"], "question": "choose the stand that is far away from the oven. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is closer to the oven. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is close to the oven. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 46], "object_names": ["doorframe", "oven"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is near the oven. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 46], "object_names": ["cup", "oven"], "question": "the cup that is farthest from the oven. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 46], "object_names": ["cup", "oven"], "question": "the cup that is far from the oven. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 46], "object_names": ["cup", "oven"], "question": "the cup that is far away from the oven. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 46], "object_names": ["carpet", "oven"], "question": "choose the carpet that is closer to the oven. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 46], "object_names": ["carpet", "oven"], "question": "choose the carpet that is close to the oven. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 46], "object_names": ["carpet", "oven"], "question": "choose the carpet that is near the oven. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 46], "object_names": ["picture", "oven"], "question": "choose the picture that is closer to the oven. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 46], "object_names": ["picture", "oven"], "question": "choose the picture that is close to the oven. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 46], "object_names": ["picture", "oven"], "question": "choose the picture that is near the oven. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 46], "object_names": ["towel", "oven"], "question": "find the towel that is closer to the oven. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 46], "object_names": ["towel", "oven"], "question": "find the towel that is close to the oven. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 46], "object_names": ["towel", "oven"], "question": "find the towel that is near the oven. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 47], "object_names": ["table", "basket"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the basket. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 47], "object_names": ["table", "basket"], "question": "select the table that is close to the basket. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 47], "object_names": ["table", "basket"], "question": "select the table that is near the basket. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 47], "object_names": ["curtain", "basket"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the basket. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 47], "object_names": ["curtain", "basket"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the basket. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 47], "object_names": ["curtain", "basket"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the basket. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 47], "object_names": ["curtain", "basket"], "question": "the curtain that is farthest from the basket. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 47], "object_names": ["curtain", "basket"], "question": "the curtain that is far from the basket. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 47], "object_names": ["curtain", "basket"], "question": "the curtain that is far away from the basket. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 47], "object_names": ["bin", "basket"], "question": "find the bin that is closer to the basket. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 47], "object_names": ["bin", "basket"], "question": "find the bin that is close to the basket. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 47], "object_names": ["bin", "basket"], "question": "find the bin that is near the basket. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 47], "object_names": ["backpack", "basket"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the basket. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63, 47], "object_names": ["backpack", "basket"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the basket. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 47], "object_names": ["backpack", "basket"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the basket. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 47], "object_names": ["backpack", "basket"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the basket. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 47], "object_names": ["backpack", "basket"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the basket. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 47], "object_names": ["backpack", "basket"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the basket. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 47], "object_names": ["stool", "basket"], "question": "select the stool that is closer to the basket. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 47], "object_names": ["stool", "basket"], "question": "select the stool that is close to the basket. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 47], "object_names": ["stool", "basket"], "question": "select the stool that is near the basket. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 47], "object_names": ["stool", "basket"], "question": "the stool that is farthest from the basket. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 47], "object_names": ["stool", "basket"], "question": "the stool that is far from the basket. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 47], "object_names": ["stool", "basket"], "question": "the stool that is far away from the basket. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 47], "object_names": ["stand", "basket"], "question": "the stand that is farthest from the basket. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 47], "object_names": ["stand", "basket"], "question": "the stand that is far from the basket. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 47], "object_names": ["stand", "basket"], "question": "the stand that is far away from the basket. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 47], "object_names": ["doorframe", "basket"], "question": "find the doorframe that is farthest from the basket. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 47], "object_names": ["doorframe", "basket"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far from the basket. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 47], "object_names": ["doorframe", "basket"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far away from the basket. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 47], "object_names": ["cup", "basket"], "question": "find the cup that is closer to the basket. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 47], "object_names": ["cup", "basket"], "question": "find the cup that is close to the basket. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 47], "object_names": ["cup", "basket"], "question": "find the cup that is near the basket. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 47], "object_names": ["carpet", "basket"], "question": "find the carpet that is closer to the basket. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 47], "object_names": ["carpet", "basket"], "question": "find the carpet that is close to the basket. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 47], "object_names": ["carpet", "basket"], "question": "find the carpet that is near the basket. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 47], "object_names": ["picture", "basket"], "question": "the picture that is next to the basket. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 47], "object_names": ["picture", "basket"], "question": "the picture that is next to the basket. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 47], "object_names": ["picture", "basket"], "question": "the picture that is next to the basket. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 47], "object_names": ["towel", "basket"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the basket. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 47], "object_names": ["towel", "basket"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the basket. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 47], "object_names": ["towel", "basket"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the basket. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 48], "object_names": ["table", "guitar"], "question": "choose the table that is closer to the guitar. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 48], "object_names": ["table", "guitar"], "question": "choose the table that is close to the guitar. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 48], "object_names": ["table", "guitar"], "question": "choose the table that is near the guitar. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 48], "object_names": ["curtain", "guitar"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the guitar. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 48], "object_names": ["curtain", "guitar"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the guitar. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 48], "object_names": ["curtain", "guitar"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the guitar. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 48], "object_names": ["curtain", "guitar"], "question": "the curtain that is farthest from the guitar. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 48], "object_names": ["curtain", "guitar"], "question": "the curtain that is far from the guitar. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 48], "object_names": ["curtain", "guitar"], "question": "the curtain that is far away from the guitar. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 48], "object_names": ["bin", "guitar"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the guitar. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 48], "object_names": ["bin", "guitar"], "question": "the bin that is far from the guitar. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 48], "object_names": ["bin", "guitar"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the guitar. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63, 48], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the guitar. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 48], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the guitar. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 48], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the guitar. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 48], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the guitar. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 48], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the guitar. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 48], "object_names": ["backpack", "guitar"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the guitar. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 48], "object_names": ["stool", "guitar"], "question": "select the stool that is closer to the guitar. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 48], "object_names": ["stool", "guitar"], "question": "select the stool that is close to the guitar. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 48], "object_names": ["stool", "guitar"], "question": "select the stool that is near the guitar. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 48], "object_names": ["stool", "guitar"], "question": "choose the stool that is farthest from the guitar. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 48], "object_names": ["stool", "guitar"], "question": "choose the stool that is far from the guitar. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 48], "object_names": ["stool", "guitar"], "question": "choose the stool that is far away from the guitar. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 48], "object_names": ["stand", "guitar"], "question": "find the stand that is farthest from the guitar. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 48], "object_names": ["stand", "guitar"], "question": "find the stand that is far from the guitar. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 48], "object_names": ["stand", "guitar"], "question": "find the stand that is far away from the guitar. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 48], "object_names": ["doorframe", "guitar"], "question": "the doorframe that is farthest from the guitar. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 48], "object_names": ["doorframe", "guitar"], "question": "the doorframe that is far from the guitar. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 48], "object_names": ["doorframe", "guitar"], "question": "the doorframe that is far away from the guitar. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 48], "object_names": ["cup", "guitar"], "question": "select the cup that is closer to the guitar. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 48], "object_names": ["cup", "guitar"], "question": "select the cup that is close to the guitar. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 48], "object_names": ["cup", "guitar"], "question": "select the cup that is near the guitar. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "guitar"], "question": "choose the carpet that is closer to the guitar. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "guitar"], "question": "choose the carpet that is close to the guitar. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 48], "object_names": ["carpet", "guitar"], "question": "choose the carpet that is near the guitar. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 48], "object_names": ["picture", "guitar"], "question": "the picture that is closer to the guitar. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 48], "object_names": ["picture", "guitar"], "question": "the picture that is close to the guitar. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 48], "object_names": ["picture", "guitar"], "question": "the picture that is near the guitar. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 48], "object_names": ["towel", "guitar"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the guitar. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 48], "object_names": ["towel", "guitar"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the guitar. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 48], "object_names": ["towel", "guitar"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the guitar. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 49], "object_names": ["table", "tissue box"], "question": "find the table that is closer to the tissue. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 49], "object_names": ["table", "tissue box"], "question": "find the table that is close to the tissue. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 49], "object_names": ["table", "tissue box"], "question": "find the table that is near the tissue. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 49], "object_names": ["table", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the table that is farthest from the tissue. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 49], "object_names": ["table", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the table that is far from the tissue. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 49], "object_names": ["table", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the table that is far away from the tissue. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the curtain that is closer to the tissue. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the curtain that is close to the tissue. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the curtain that is near the tissue. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the tissue. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the tissue. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 49], "object_names": ["curtain", "tissue box"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the tissue. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 49], "object_names": ["bin", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the bin that is closer to the tissue. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 49], "object_names": ["bin", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the bin that is close to the tissue. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 49], "object_names": ["bin", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the bin that is near the tissue. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 49], "object_names": ["backpack", "tissue box"], "question": "select the backpack that is closer to the tissue. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 49], "object_names": ["backpack", "tissue box"], "question": "select the backpack that is close to the tissue. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 49], "object_names": ["backpack", "tissue box"], "question": "select the backpack that is near the tissue. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 49], "object_names": ["backpack", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the tissue. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 49], "object_names": ["backpack", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the tissue. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 49], "object_names": ["backpack", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the tissue. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 49], "object_names": ["stool", "tissue box"], "question": "select the stool that is closer to the tissue. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 49], "object_names": ["stool", "tissue box"], "question": "select the stool that is close to the tissue. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 49], "object_names": ["stool", "tissue box"], "question": "select the stool that is near the tissue. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 49], "object_names": ["stool", "tissue box"], "question": "the stool that is farthest from the tissue. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 49], "object_names": ["stool", "tissue box"], "question": "the stool that is far from the tissue. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 49], "object_names": ["stool", "tissue box"], "question": "the stool that is far away from the tissue. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 49], "object_names": ["stand", "tissue box"], "question": "the stand that is beside the tissue. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 49], "object_names": ["stand", "tissue box"], "question": "the stand that is beside the tissue. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 49], "object_names": ["stand", "tissue box"], "question": "the stand that is beside the tissue. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 49], "object_names": ["doorframe", "tissue box"], "question": "find the doorframe that is farthest from the tissue. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 49], "object_names": ["doorframe", "tissue box"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far from the tissue. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 49], "object_names": ["doorframe", "tissue box"], "question": "find the doorframe that is far away from the tissue. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 49], "object_names": ["cup", "tissue box"], "question": "the cup that is closer to the tissue. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 49], "object_names": ["cup", "tissue box"], "question": "the cup that is close to the tissue. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 49], "object_names": ["cup", "tissue box"], "question": "the cup that is near the tissue. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 49], "object_names": ["carpet", "tissue box"], "question": "the carpet that is farthest from the tissue. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 49], "object_names": ["carpet", "tissue box"], "question": "the carpet that is far from the tissue. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 49], "object_names": ["carpet", "tissue box"], "question": "the carpet that is far away from the tissue. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 49], "object_names": ["picture", "tissue box"], "question": "the picture that is farthest from the tissue. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 49], "object_names": ["picture", "tissue box"], "question": "the picture that is far from the tissue. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 49], "object_names": ["picture", "tissue box"], "question": "the picture that is far away from the tissue. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 49], "object_names": ["towel", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the towel that is farthest from the tissue. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 49], "object_names": ["towel", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the towel that is far from the tissue. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 49], "object_names": ["towel", "tissue box"], "question": "choose the towel that is far away from the tissue. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 52], "object_names": ["table", "dish rack"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the dish. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 52], "object_names": ["table", "dish rack"], "question": "select the table that is close to the dish. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 52], "object_names": ["table", "dish rack"], "question": "select the table that is near the dish. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 52], "object_names": ["table", "dish rack"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the dish. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 52], "object_names": ["table", "dish rack"], "question": "the table that is far from the dish. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 52], "object_names": ["table", "dish rack"], "question": "the table that is far away from the dish. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 52], "object_names": ["curtain", "dish rack"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the dish. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 52], "object_names": ["curtain", "dish rack"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the dish. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 52], "object_names": ["curtain", "dish rack"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the dish. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 52], "object_names": ["curtain", "dish rack"], "question": "choose the curtain that is farthest from the dish. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 52], "object_names": ["curtain", "dish rack"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far from the dish. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 52], "object_names": ["curtain", "dish rack"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far away from the dish. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 52], "object_names": ["bin", "dish rack"], "question": "find the bin that is farthest from the dish. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 52], "object_names": ["bin", "dish rack"], "question": "find the bin that is far from the dish. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 52], "object_names": ["bin", "dish rack"], "question": "find the bin that is far away from the dish. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 52], "object_names": ["backpack", "dish rack"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the dish. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 52], "object_names": ["backpack", "dish rack"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the dish. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 52], "object_names": ["backpack", "dish rack"], "question": "the backpack that is near the dish. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 52], "object_names": ["backpack", "dish rack"], "question": "select the backpack that is farthest from the dish. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 52], "object_names": ["backpack", "dish rack"], "question": "select the backpack that is far from the dish. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 52], "object_names": ["backpack", "dish rack"], "question": "select the backpack that is far away from the dish. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 52], "object_names": ["stool", "dish rack"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the dish. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 52], "object_names": ["stool", "dish rack"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the dish. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 52], "object_names": ["stool", "dish rack"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the dish. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 52], "object_names": ["stand", "dish rack"], "question": "select the stand that is farthest from the dish. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 52], "object_names": ["stand", "dish rack"], "question": "select the stand that is far from the dish. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 52], "object_names": ["stand", "dish rack"], "question": "select the stand that is far away from the dish. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "the doorframe that is closer to the dish. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "the doorframe that is close to the dish. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 52], "object_names": ["doorframe", "dish rack"], "question": "the doorframe that is near the dish. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 52], "object_names": ["cup", "dish rack"], "question": "choose the cup that is farthest from the dish. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 52], "object_names": ["cup", "dish rack"], "question": "choose the cup that is far from the dish. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 52], "object_names": ["cup", "dish rack"], "question": "choose the cup that is far away from the dish. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 52], "object_names": ["towel", "dish rack"], "question": "the towel that is closer to the dish. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 52], "object_names": ["towel", "dish rack"], "question": "the towel that is close to the dish. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 52], "object_names": ["towel", "dish rack"], "question": "the towel that is near the dish. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 52], "object_names": ["towel", "dish rack"], "question": "the towel that is farthest from the dish. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [168, 52], "object_names": ["towel", "dish rack"], "question": "the towel that is far from the dish. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168, 52], "object_names": ["towel", "dish rack"], "question": "the towel that is far away from the dish. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 53], "object_names": ["table", "microwave"], "question": "choose the table that is closer to the microwave. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 53], "object_names": ["table", "microwave"], "question": "choose the table that is close to the microwave. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 53], "object_names": ["table", "microwave"], "question": "choose the table that is near the microwave. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 53], "object_names": ["table", "microwave"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the microwave. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 53], "object_names": ["table", "microwave"], "question": "the table that is far from the microwave. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 53], "object_names": ["table", "microwave"], "question": "the table that is far away from the microwave. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 53], "object_names": ["curtain", "microwave"], "question": "choose the curtain that is closer to the microwave. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 53], "object_names": ["curtain", "microwave"], "question": "choose the curtain that is close to the microwave. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 53], "object_names": ["curtain", "microwave"], "question": "choose the curtain that is near the microwave. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 53], "object_names": ["curtain", "microwave"], "question": "the curtain that is farthest from the microwave. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 53], "object_names": ["curtain", "microwave"], "question": "the curtain that is far from the microwave. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 53], "object_names": ["curtain", "microwave"], "question": "the curtain that is far away from the microwave. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "find the bin that is farthest from the microwave. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "find the bin that is far from the microwave. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 53], "object_names": ["bin", "microwave"], "question": "find the bin that is far away from the microwave. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 53], "object_names": ["backpack", "microwave"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the microwave. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 53], "object_names": ["backpack", "microwave"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the microwave. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 53], "object_names": ["backpack", "microwave"], "question": "the backpack that is near the microwave. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 53], "object_names": ["backpack", "microwave"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the microwave. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 53], "object_names": ["backpack", "microwave"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the microwave. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 53], "object_names": ["backpack", "microwave"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the microwave. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 53], "object_names": ["stool", "microwave"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the microwave. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 53], "object_names": ["stool", "microwave"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the microwave. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 53], "object_names": ["stool", "microwave"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the microwave. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 53], "object_names": ["stand", "microwave"], "question": "choose the stand that is farthest from the microwave. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 53], "object_names": ["stand", "microwave"], "question": "choose the stand that is far from the microwave. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 53], "object_names": ["stand", "microwave"], "question": "choose the stand that is far away from the microwave. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "the doorframe that is closer to the microwave. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "the doorframe that is close to the microwave. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 53], "object_names": ["doorframe", "microwave"], "question": "the doorframe that is near the microwave. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 53], "object_names": ["cup", "microwave"], "question": "find the cup that is farthest from the microwave. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 53], "object_names": ["cup", "microwave"], "question": "find the cup that is far from the microwave. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 53], "object_names": ["cup", "microwave"], "question": "find the cup that is far away from the microwave. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 53], "object_names": ["carpet", "microwave"], "question": "the carpet that is closer to the microwave. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 53], "object_names": ["carpet", "microwave"], "question": "the carpet that is close to the microwave. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 53], "object_names": ["carpet", "microwave"], "question": "the carpet that is near the microwave. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 53], "object_names": ["picture", "microwave"], "question": "choose the picture that is closer to the microwave. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 53], "object_names": ["picture", "microwave"], "question": "choose the picture that is close to the microwave. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 53], "object_names": ["picture", "microwave"], "question": "choose the picture that is near the microwave. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 53], "object_names": ["towel", "microwave"], "question": "find the towel that is closer to the microwave. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 53], "object_names": ["towel", "microwave"], "question": "find the towel that is close to the microwave. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 53], "object_names": ["towel", "microwave"], "question": "find the towel that is near the microwave. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 54], "object_names": ["table", "toaster"], "question": "the table that is closer to the toaster. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3, 54], "object_names": ["table", "toaster"], "question": "the table that is close to the toaster. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 54], "object_names": ["table", "toaster"], "question": "the table that is near the toaster. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 54], "object_names": ["table", "toaster"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the toaster. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36, 54], "object_names": ["table", "toaster"], "question": "the table that is far from the toaster. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 54], "object_names": ["table", "toaster"], "question": "the table that is far away from the toaster. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 54], "object_names": ["curtain", "toaster"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the toaster. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 54], "object_names": ["curtain", "toaster"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the toaster. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 54], "object_names": ["curtain", "toaster"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the toaster. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 54], "object_names": ["curtain", "toaster"], "question": "choose the curtain that is farthest from the toaster. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 54], "object_names": ["curtain", "toaster"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far from the toaster. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 54], "object_names": ["curtain", "toaster"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far away from the toaster. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the toaster. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [15, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "the bin that is far from the toaster. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 54], "object_names": ["bin", "toaster"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the toaster. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 54], "object_names": ["backpack", "toaster"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the toaster. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 54], "object_names": ["backpack", "toaster"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the toaster. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 54], "object_names": ["backpack", "toaster"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the toaster. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 54], "object_names": ["backpack", "toaster"], "question": "find the backpack that is farthest from the toaster. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 54], "object_names": ["backpack", "toaster"], "question": "find the backpack that is far from the toaster. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 54], "object_names": ["backpack", "toaster"], "question": "find the backpack that is far away from the toaster. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 54], "object_names": ["stand", "toaster"], "question": "the stand that is farthest from the toaster. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 54], "object_names": ["stand", "toaster"], "question": "the stand that is far from the toaster. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 54], "object_names": ["stand", "toaster"], "question": "the stand that is far away from the toaster. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "select the doorframe that is closer to the toaster. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "select the doorframe that is close to the toaster. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 54], "object_names": ["doorframe", "toaster"], "question": "select the doorframe that is near the toaster. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 54], "object_names": ["cup", "toaster"], "question": "select the cup that is farthest from the toaster. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 54], "object_names": ["cup", "toaster"], "question": "select the cup that is far from the toaster. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 54], "object_names": ["cup", "toaster"], "question": "select the cup that is far away from the toaster. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 54], "object_names": ["carpet", "toaster"], "question": "the carpet that is closer to the toaster. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 54], "object_names": ["carpet", "toaster"], "question": "the carpet that is close to the toaster. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 54], "object_names": ["carpet", "toaster"], "question": "the carpet that is near the toaster. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 54], "object_names": ["picture", "toaster"], "question": "find the picture that is closer to the toaster. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 54], "object_names": ["picture", "toaster"], "question": "find the picture that is close to the toaster. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 54], "object_names": ["picture", "toaster"], "question": "find the picture that is near the toaster. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 54], "object_names": ["towel", "toaster"], "question": "find the towel that is closer to the toaster. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 54], "object_names": ["towel", "toaster"], "question": "find the towel that is close to the toaster. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 54], "object_names": ["towel", "toaster"], "question": "find the towel that is near the toaster. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 55], "object_names": ["table", "door"], "question": "find the table that is closer to the door. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 55], "object_names": ["table", "door"], "question": "find the table that is close to the door. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 55], "object_names": ["table", "door"], "question": "find the table that is near the door. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 55], "object_names": ["table", "door"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the door. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 55], "object_names": ["table", "door"], "question": "the table that is far from the door. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 55], "object_names": ["table", "door"], "question": "the table that is far away from the door. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 55], "object_names": ["curtain", "door"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the door. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 55], "object_names": ["curtain", "door"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the door. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 55], "object_names": ["curtain", "door"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the door. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 55], "object_names": ["curtain", "door"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the door. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 55], "object_names": ["curtain", "door"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the door. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 55], "object_names": ["curtain", "door"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the door. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 55], "object_names": ["bin", "door"], "question": "choose the bin that is farthest from the door. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 55], "object_names": ["bin", "door"], "question": "choose the bin that is far from the door. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 55], "object_names": ["bin", "door"], "question": "choose the bin that is far away from the door. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 55], "object_names": ["backpack", "door"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the door. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 55], "object_names": ["backpack", "door"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the door. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 55], "object_names": ["backpack", "door"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the door. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 55], "object_names": ["backpack", "door"], "question": "select the backpack that is farthest from the door. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 55], "object_names": ["backpack", "door"], "question": "select the backpack that is far from the door. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 55], "object_names": ["backpack", "door"], "question": "select the backpack that is far away from the door. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 55], "object_names": ["stool", "door"], "question": "find the stool that is closer to the door. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 55], "object_names": ["stool", "door"], "question": "find the stool that is close to the door. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 55], "object_names": ["stool", "door"], "question": "find the stool that is near the door. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 55], "object_names": ["stool", "door"], "question": "the stool that is farthest from the door. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 55], "object_names": ["stool", "door"], "question": "the stool that is far from the door. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 55], "object_names": ["stool", "door"], "question": "the stool that is far away from the door. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 55], "object_names": ["stand", "door"], "question": "the stand that is farthest from the door. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 55], "object_names": ["stand", "door"], "question": "the stand that is far from the door. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 55], "object_names": ["stand", "door"], "question": "the stand that is far away from the door. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "choose the cup that is closer to the door. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "choose the cup that is close to the door. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 55], "object_names": ["cup", "door"], "question": "choose the cup that is near the door. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 55], "object_names": ["carpet", "door"], "question": "select the carpet that is closer to the door. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 55], "object_names": ["carpet", "door"], "question": "select the carpet that is close to the door. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 55], "object_names": ["carpet", "door"], "question": "select the carpet that is near the door. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 55], "object_names": ["picture", "door"], "question": "the picture that is closer to the door. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 55], "object_names": ["picture", "door"], "question": "the picture that is close to the door. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging on the wall"], "object_ids": [159, 55], "object_names": ["picture", "door"], "question": "the picture that is near the door. What is placement of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "choose the towel that is closer to the door. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "choose the towel that is close to the door. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 55], "object_names": ["towel", "door"], "question": "choose the towel that is near the door. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["vertically on a beige carpet"], "object_ids": [35, 57], "object_names": ["table", "shelf"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the shelf. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35, 57], "object_names": ["table", "shelf"], "question": "select the table that is close to the shelf. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [35, 57], "object_names": ["table", "shelf"], "question": "select the table that is near the shelf. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 57], "object_names": ["table", "shelf"], "question": "select the table that is farthest from the shelf. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 57], "object_names": ["table", "shelf"], "question": "select the table that is far from the shelf. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36, 57], "object_names": ["table", "shelf"], "question": "select the table that is far away from the shelf. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 57], "object_names": ["curtain", "shelf"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the shelf. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 57], "object_names": ["curtain", "shelf"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the shelf. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 57], "object_names": ["curtain", "shelf"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the shelf. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 57], "object_names": ["curtain", "shelf"], "question": "choose the curtain that is farthest from the shelf. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 57], "object_names": ["curtain", "shelf"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far from the shelf. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 57], "object_names": ["curtain", "shelf"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far away from the shelf. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standing upright"], "object_ids": [13, 57], "object_names": ["bin", "shelf"], "question": "find the bin that is closer to the shelf. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [13, 57], "object_names": ["bin", "shelf"], "question": "find the bin that is close to the shelf. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["sits on the floor"], "object_ids": [13, 57], "object_names": ["bin", "shelf"], "question": "find the bin that is near the shelf. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 57], "object_names": ["bin", "shelf"], "question": "choose the bin that is farthest from the shelf. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 57], "object_names": ["bin", "shelf"], "question": "choose the bin that is far from the shelf. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 57], "object_names": ["bin", "shelf"], "question": "choose the bin that is far away from the shelf. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 57], "object_names": ["backpack", "shelf"], "question": "choose the backpack that is closer to the shelf. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 57], "object_names": ["backpack", "shelf"], "question": "choose the backpack that is close to the shelf. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 57], "object_names": ["backpack", "shelf"], "question": "choose the backpack that is near the shelf. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 57], "object_names": ["backpack", "shelf"], "question": "find the backpack that is farthest from the shelf. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 57], "object_names": ["backpack", "shelf"], "question": "find the backpack that is far from the shelf. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 57], "object_names": ["backpack", "shelf"], "question": "find the backpack that is far away from the shelf. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "the stool that is farthest from the shelf. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "the stool that is far from the shelf. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 57], "object_names": ["stool", "shelf"], "question": "the stool that is far away from the shelf. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 57], "object_names": ["doorframe", "shelf"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is closer to the shelf. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 57], "object_names": ["doorframe", "shelf"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is close to the shelf. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 57], "object_names": ["doorframe", "shelf"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is near the shelf. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 57], "object_names": ["cup", "shelf"], "question": "the cup that is farthest from the shelf. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 57], "object_names": ["cup", "shelf"], "question": "the cup that is far from the shelf. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 57], "object_names": ["cup", "shelf"], "question": "the cup that is far away from the shelf. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 57], "object_names": ["carpet", "shelf"], "question": "select the carpet that is farthest from the shelf. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 57], "object_names": ["carpet", "shelf"], "question": "select the carpet that is far from the shelf. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 57], "object_names": ["carpet", "shelf"], "question": "select the carpet that is far away from the shelf. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 57], "object_names": ["towel", "shelf"], "question": "choose the towel that is closer to the shelf. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 57], "object_names": ["towel", "shelf"], "question": "choose the towel that is close to the shelf. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 57], "object_names": ["towel", "shelf"], "question": "choose the towel that is near the shelf. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 57], "object_names": ["towel", "shelf"], "question": "choose the towel that is farthest from the shelf. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 57], "object_names": ["towel", "shelf"], "question": "choose the towel that is far from the shelf. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 57], "object_names": ["towel", "shelf"], "question": "choose the towel that is far away from the shelf. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["vertically on a beige carpet"], "object_ids": [35, 58], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the bicycle. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["vertically on a beige carpet"], "object_ids": [35, 58], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle"], "question": "select the table that is close to the bicycle. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [35, 58], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle"], "question": "select the table that is near the bicycle. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3, 58], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the bicycle. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 58], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle"], "question": "the table that is far from the bicycle. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3, 58], "object_names": ["table", "bicycle"], "question": "the table that is far away from the bicycle. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 58], "object_names": ["curtain", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the curtain that is closer to the bicycle. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 58], "object_names": ["curtain", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the curtain that is close to the bicycle. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 58], "object_names": ["curtain", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the curtain that is near the bicycle. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 58], "object_names": ["curtain", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the curtain that is farthest from the bicycle. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 58], "object_names": ["curtain", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far from the bicycle. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 58], "object_names": ["curtain", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far away from the bicycle. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 58], "object_names": ["bin", "bicycle"], "question": "select the bin that is closer to the bicycle. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 58], "object_names": ["bin", "bicycle"], "question": "select the bin that is close to the bicycle. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 58], "object_names": ["bin", "bicycle"], "question": "select the bin that is near the bicycle. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14, 58], "object_names": ["bin", "bicycle"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the bicycle. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14, 58], "object_names": ["bin", "bicycle"], "question": "the bin that is far from the bicycle. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 58], "object_names": ["bin", "bicycle"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the bicycle. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "bicycle"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the bicycle. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "bicycle"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the bicycle. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "bicycle"], "question": "the backpack that is near the bicycle. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "bicycle"], "question": "select the backpack that is farthest from the bicycle. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "bicycle"], "question": "select the backpack that is far from the bicycle. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 58], "object_names": ["backpack", "bicycle"], "question": "select the backpack that is far away from the bicycle. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 58], "object_names": ["stool", "bicycle"], "question": "find the stool that is farthest from the bicycle. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 58], "object_names": ["stool", "bicycle"], "question": "find the stool that is far from the bicycle. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 58], "object_names": ["stool", "bicycle"], "question": "find the stool that is far away from the bicycle. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 58], "object_names": ["stand", "bicycle"], "question": "the stand that is closer to the bicycle. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 58], "object_names": ["stand", "bicycle"], "question": "the stand that is close to the bicycle. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 58], "object_names": ["stand", "bicycle"], "question": "the stand that is near the bicycle. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["synthetic and leather", "Leather"], "object_ids": [59, 58], "object_names": ["shoe", "bicycle"], "question": "the shoe that is closer to the bicycle. What is material of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["rounded toe", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59, 58], "object_names": ["shoe", "bicycle"], "question": "the shoe that is close to the bicycle. What is shape of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right"], "object_ids": [59, 58], "object_names": ["shoe", "bicycle"], "question": "the shoe that is near the bicycle. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [162, 58], "object_names": ["shoe", "bicycle"], "question": "find the shoe that is farthest from the bicycle. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [162, 58], "object_names": ["shoe", "bicycle"], "question": "find the shoe that is far from the bicycle. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["good condition, showing no signs of wear or damage"], "object_ids": [162, 58], "object_names": ["shoe", "bicycle"], "question": "find the shoe that is far away from the bicycle. What is state of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 58], "object_names": ["doorframe", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is farthest from the bicycle. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 58], "object_names": ["doorframe", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is far from the bicycle. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 58], "object_names": ["doorframe", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is far away from the bicycle. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 58], "object_names": ["cup", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the cup that is farthest from the bicycle. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 58], "object_names": ["cup", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the cup that is far from the bicycle. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 58], "object_names": ["cup", "bicycle"], "question": "choose the cup that is far away from the bicycle. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 58], "object_names": ["carpet", "bicycle"], "question": "find the carpet that is farthest from the bicycle. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 58], "object_names": ["carpet", "bicycle"], "question": "find the carpet that is far from the bicycle. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["well-preserved, without any visible stains or damage"], "object_ids": [150, 58], "object_names": ["carpet", "bicycle"], "question": "find the carpet that is far away from the bicycle. What is state of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [168, 58], "object_names": ["towel", "bicycle"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the bicycle. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 58], "object_names": ["towel", "bicycle"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the bicycle. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 58], "object_names": ["towel", "bicycle"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the bicycle. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 65], "object_names": ["table", "mirror"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the mirror. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 65], "object_names": ["table", "mirror"], "question": "select the table that is close to the mirror. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 65], "object_names": ["table", "mirror"], "question": "select the table that is near the mirror. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 65], "object_names": ["table", "mirror"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the mirror. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36, 65], "object_names": ["table", "mirror"], "question": "the table that is far from the mirror. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["used to put objects on top"], "object_ids": [36, 65], "object_names": ["table", "mirror"], "question": "the table that is far away from the mirror. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 65], "object_names": ["curtain", "mirror"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the mirror. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["hangs vertically on the window"], "object_ids": [7, 65], "object_names": ["curtain", "mirror"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the mirror. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 65], "object_names": ["curtain", "mirror"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the mirror. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 65], "object_names": ["curtain", "mirror"], "question": "the curtain that is farthest from the mirror. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 65], "object_names": ["curtain", "mirror"], "question": "the curtain that is far from the mirror. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 65], "object_names": ["curtain", "mirror"], "question": "the curtain that is far away from the mirror. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [15, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "choose the bin that is farthest from the mirror. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "choose the bin that is far from the mirror. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 65], "object_names": ["bin", "mirror"], "question": "choose the bin that is far away from the mirror. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 65], "object_names": ["backpack", "mirror"], "question": "find the backpack that is closer to the mirror. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 65], "object_names": ["backpack", "mirror"], "question": "find the backpack that is close to the mirror. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["looks new, without any noticeable wear or damage"], "object_ids": [63, 65], "object_names": ["backpack", "mirror"], "question": "find the backpack that is near the mirror. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 65], "object_names": ["backpack", "mirror"], "question": "select the backpack that is farthest from the mirror. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 65], "object_names": ["backpack", "mirror"], "question": "select the backpack that is far from the mirror. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 65], "object_names": ["backpack", "mirror"], "question": "select the backpack that is far away from the mirror. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 65], "object_names": ["stool", "mirror"], "question": "find the stool that is closer to the mirror. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 65], "object_names": ["stool", "mirror"], "question": "find the stool that is close to the mirror. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 65], "object_names": ["stool", "mirror"], "question": "find the stool that is near the mirror. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 65], "object_names": ["stool", "mirror"], "question": "the stool that is farthest from the mirror. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 65], "object_names": ["stool", "mirror"], "question": "the stool that is far from the mirror. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 65], "object_names": ["stool", "mirror"], "question": "the stool that is far away from the mirror. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 65], "object_names": ["stand", "mirror"], "question": "select the stand that is farthest from the mirror. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 65], "object_names": ["stand", "mirror"], "question": "select the stand that is far from the mirror. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 65], "object_names": ["stand", "mirror"], "question": "select the stand that is far away from the mirror. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "the doorframe that is farthest from the mirror. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "the doorframe that is far from the mirror. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 65], "object_names": ["doorframe", "mirror"], "question": "the doorframe that is far away from the mirror. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 65], "object_names": ["cup", "mirror"], "question": "find the cup that is beside the mirror. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 65], "object_names": ["cup", "mirror"], "question": "find the cup that is beside the mirror. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 65], "object_names": ["cup", "mirror"], "question": "find the cup that is beside the mirror. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 65], "object_names": ["carpet", "mirror"], "question": "select the carpet that is closer to the mirror. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 65], "object_names": ["carpet", "mirror"], "question": "select the carpet that is close to the mirror. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 65], "object_names": ["carpet", "mirror"], "question": "select the carpet that is near the mirror. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 65], "object_names": ["picture", "mirror"], "question": "the picture that is closer to the mirror. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 65], "object_names": ["picture", "mirror"], "question": "the picture that is close to the mirror. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 65], "object_names": ["picture", "mirror"], "question": "the picture that is near the mirror. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "choose the towel that is closer to the mirror. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "choose the towel that is close to the mirror. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "choose the towel that is near the mirror. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the mirror. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the mirror. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 65], "object_names": ["towel", "mirror"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the mirror. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 67], "object_names": ["table", "case"], "question": "choose the table that is closer to the case. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 67], "object_names": ["table", "case"], "question": "choose the table that is close to the case. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3, 67], "object_names": ["table", "case"], "question": "choose the table that is near the case. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 67], "object_names": ["table", "case"], "question": "find the table that is farthest from the case. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 67], "object_names": ["table", "case"], "question": "find the table that is far from the case. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 67], "object_names": ["table", "case"], "question": "find the table that is far away from the case. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 67], "object_names": ["curtain", "case"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the case. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 67], "object_names": ["curtain", "case"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the case. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 67], "object_names": ["curtain", "case"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the case. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [7, 67], "object_names": ["curtain", "case"], "question": "select the curtain that is farthest from the case. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 67], "object_names": ["curtain", "case"], "question": "select the curtain that is far from the case. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 67], "object_names": ["curtain", "case"], "question": "select the curtain that is far away from the case. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["sits on the floor"], "object_ids": [13, 67], "object_names": ["bin", "case"], "question": "choose the bin that is closer to the case. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [13, 67], "object_names": ["bin", "case"], "question": "choose the bin that is close to the case. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["sits on the floor"], "object_ids": [13, 67], "object_names": ["bin", "case"], "question": "choose the bin that is near the case. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 67], "object_names": ["bin", "case"], "question": "choose the bin that is farthest from the case. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 67], "object_names": ["bin", "case"], "question": "choose the bin that is far from the case. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 67], "object_names": ["bin", "case"], "question": "choose the bin that is far away from the case. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 67], "object_names": ["backpack", "case"], "question": "choose the backpack that is closer to the case. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 67], "object_names": ["backpack", "case"], "question": "choose the backpack that is close to the case. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["black or dark brown", "Black"], "object_ids": [19, 67], "object_names": ["backpack", "case"], "question": "choose the backpack that is near the case. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 67], "object_names": ["backpack", "case"], "question": "find the backpack that is farthest from the case. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 67], "object_names": ["backpack", "case"], "question": "find the backpack that is far from the case. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 67], "object_names": ["backpack", "case"], "question": "find the backpack that is far away from the case. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [29, 67], "object_names": ["stool", "case"], "question": "choose the stool that is farthest from the case. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 67], "object_names": ["stool", "case"], "question": "choose the stool that is far from the case. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 67], "object_names": ["stool", "case"], "question": "choose the stool that is far away from the case. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 67], "object_names": ["stand", "case"], "question": "choose the stand that is farthest from the case. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 67], "object_names": ["stand", "case"], "question": "choose the stand that is far from the case. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 67], "object_names": ["stand", "case"], "question": "choose the stand that is far away from the case. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 67], "object_names": ["doorframe", "case"], "question": "find the doorframe that is closer to the case. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 67], "object_names": ["doorframe", "case"], "question": "find the doorframe that is close to the case. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 67], "object_names": ["doorframe", "case"], "question": "find the doorframe that is near the case. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 67], "object_names": ["cup", "case"], "question": "choose the cup that is farthest from the case. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 67], "object_names": ["cup", "case"], "question": "choose the cup that is far from the case. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 67], "object_names": ["cup", "case"], "question": "choose the cup that is far away from the case. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 67], "object_names": ["carpet", "case"], "question": "the carpet that is farthest from the case. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 67], "object_names": ["carpet", "case"], "question": "the carpet that is far from the case. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 67], "object_names": ["carpet", "case"], "question": "the carpet that is far away from the case. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 67], "object_names": ["towel", "case"], "question": "find the towel that is closer to the case. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [180, 67], "object_names": ["towel", "case"], "question": "find the towel that is close to the case. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 67], "object_names": ["towel", "case"], "question": "find the towel that is near the case. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 67], "object_names": ["towel", "case"], "question": "select the towel that is farthest from the case. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 67], "object_names": ["towel", "case"], "question": "select the towel that is far from the case. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 67], "object_names": ["towel", "case"], "question": "select the towel that is far away from the case. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 68], "object_names": ["table", "chair"], "question": "the table that is closer to the chair. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 68], "object_names": ["table", "chair"], "question": "the table that is close to the chair. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 68], "object_names": ["table", "chair"], "question": "the table that is near the chair. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 68], "object_names": ["table", "chair"], "question": "choose the table that is farthest from the chair. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 68], "object_names": ["table", "chair"], "question": "choose the table that is far from the chair. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [3, 68], "object_names": ["table", "chair"], "question": "choose the table that is far away from the chair. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 68], "object_names": ["curtain", "chair"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the chair. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 68], "object_names": ["curtain", "chair"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the chair. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 68], "object_names": ["curtain", "chair"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the chair. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 68], "object_names": ["curtain", "chair"], "question": "choose the curtain that is farthest from the chair. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 68], "object_names": ["curtain", "chair"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far from the chair. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [6, 68], "object_names": ["curtain", "chair"], "question": "choose the curtain that is far away from the chair. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 68], "object_names": ["bin", "chair"], "question": "find the bin that is next to the chair. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 68], "object_names": ["bin", "chair"], "question": "find the bin that is next to the chair. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 68], "object_names": ["bin", "chair"], "question": "find the bin that is next to the chair. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14, 68], "object_names": ["bin", "chair"], "question": "the bin that is farthest from the chair. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 68], "object_names": ["bin", "chair"], "question": "the bin that is far from the chair. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 68], "object_names": ["bin", "chair"], "question": "the bin that is far away from the chair. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the chair. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the chair. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "the backpack that is near the chair. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "the backpack that is farthest from the chair. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["has multiple compartments and shoulder straps for carrying"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "the backpack that is far from the chair. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 68], "object_names": ["backpack", "chair"], "question": "the backpack that is far away from the chair. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 68], "object_names": ["stool", "chair"], "question": "find the stool that is closer to the chair. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 68], "object_names": ["stool", "chair"], "question": "find the stool that is close to the chair. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [29, 68], "object_names": ["stool", "chair"], "question": "find the stool that is near the chair. What is weight of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 68], "object_names": ["stool", "chair"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the chair. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["sits vertically on the floor"], "object_ids": [31, 68], "object_names": ["stool", "chair"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the chair. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 68], "object_names": ["stool", "chair"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the chair. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 68], "object_names": ["stand", "chair"], "question": "choose the stand that is closer to the chair. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 68], "object_names": ["stand", "chair"], "question": "choose the stand that is close to the chair. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 68], "object_names": ["stand", "chair"], "question": "choose the stand that is near the chair. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 68], "object_names": ["doorframe", "chair"], "question": "the doorframe that is farthest from the chair. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 68], "object_names": ["doorframe", "chair"], "question": "the doorframe that is far from the chair. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 68], "object_names": ["doorframe", "chair"], "question": "the doorframe that is far away from the chair. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 68], "object_names": ["cup", "chair"], "question": "choose the cup that is closer to the chair. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 68], "object_names": ["cup", "chair"], "question": "choose the cup that is close to the chair. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 68], "object_names": ["cup", "chair"], "question": "choose the cup that is near the chair. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [150, 68], "object_names": ["carpet", "chair"], "question": "choose the carpet that is farthest from the chair. What is size of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 68], "object_names": ["carpet", "chair"], "question": "choose the carpet that is far from the chair. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 68], "object_names": ["carpet", "chair"], "question": "choose the carpet that is far away from the chair. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 68], "object_names": ["picture", "chair"], "question": "select the picture that is farthest from the chair. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 68], "object_names": ["picture", "chair"], "question": "select the picture that is far from the chair. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 68], "object_names": ["picture", "chair"], "question": "select the picture that is far away from the chair. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["neatly hung"], "object_ids": [180, 68], "object_names": ["towel", "chair"], "question": "choose the towel that is farthest from the chair. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["subtle checkered pattern"], "object_ids": [180, 68], "object_names": ["towel", "chair"], "question": "choose the towel that is far from the chair. What is texture of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 68], "object_names": ["towel", "chair"], "question": "choose the towel that is far away from the chair. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["wooden", "Wood"], "object_ids": [36, 88], "object_names": ["table", "speaker"], "question": "choose the table that is closer to the speaker. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 88], "object_names": ["table", "speaker"], "question": "choose the table that is close to the speaker. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [36, 88], "object_names": ["table", "speaker"], "question": "choose the table that is near the speaker. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 88], "object_names": ["table", "speaker"], "question": "choose the table that is farthest from the speaker. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 88], "object_names": ["table", "speaker"], "question": "choose the table that is far from the speaker. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 88], "object_names": ["table", "speaker"], "question": "choose the table that is far away from the speaker. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the speaker. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the speaker. What is shape of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the speaker. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "find the curtain that is farthest from the speaker. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [6, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "find the curtain that is far from the speaker. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 88], "object_names": ["curtain", "speaker"], "question": "find the curtain that is far away from the speaker. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 88], "object_names": ["bin", "speaker"], "question": "the bin that is next to the speaker. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [15, 88], "object_names": ["bin", "speaker"], "question": "the bin that is next to the speaker. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 88], "object_names": ["bin", "speaker"], "question": "the bin that is next to the speaker. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63, 88], "object_names": ["backpack", "speaker"], "question": "select the backpack that is closer to the speaker. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 88], "object_names": ["backpack", "speaker"], "question": "select the backpack that is close to the speaker. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 88], "object_names": ["backpack", "speaker"], "question": "select the backpack that is near the speaker. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 88], "object_names": ["backpack", "speaker"], "question": "the backpack that is farthest from the speaker. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["nylon or canvas", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [19, 88], "object_names": ["backpack", "speaker"], "question": "the backpack that is far from the speaker. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [19, 88], "object_names": ["backpack", "speaker"], "question": "the backpack that is far away from the speaker. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [29, 88], "object_names": ["stool", "speaker"], "question": "select the stool that is closer to the speaker. What is texture of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 88], "object_names": ["stool", "speaker"], "question": "select the stool that is close to the speaker. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 88], "object_names": ["stool", "speaker"], "question": "select the stool that is near the speaker. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 88], "object_names": ["stool", "speaker"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the speaker. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 88], "object_names": ["stool", "speaker"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the speaker. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 88], "object_names": ["stool", "speaker"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the speaker. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 88], "object_names": ["stand", "speaker"], "question": "the stand that is closer to the speaker. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["storage"], "object_ids": [50, 88], "object_names": ["stand", "speaker"], "question": "the stand that is close to the speaker. What is function of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [50, 88], "object_names": ["stand", "speaker"], "question": "the stand that is near the speaker. What is state of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [162, 88], "object_names": ["shoe", "speaker"], "question": "choose the shoe that is closer to the speaker. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["black and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [162, 88], "object_names": ["shoe", "speaker"], "question": "choose the shoe that is close to the speaker. What is color of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["synthetic materials (polyester fiber and rubber)", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [162, 88], "object_names": ["shoe", "speaker"], "question": "choose the shoe that is near the speaker. What is material of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["black", "Black"], "object_ids": [59, 88], "object_names": ["shoe", "speaker"], "question": "find the shoe that is farthest from the speaker. What is color of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [59, 88], "object_names": ["shoe", "speaker"], "question": "find the shoe that is far from the speaker. What is state of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [59, 88], "object_names": ["shoe", "speaker"], "question": "find the shoe that is far away from the speaker. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["provides security"], "object_ids": [66, 88], "object_names": ["doorframe", "speaker"], "question": "the doorframe that is farthest from the speaker. What is function of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 88], "object_names": ["doorframe", "speaker"], "question": "the doorframe that is far from the speaker. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 88], "object_names": ["doorframe", "speaker"], "question": "the doorframe that is far away from the speaker. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 88], "object_names": ["cup", "speaker"], "question": "the cup that is closer to the speaker. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 88], "object_names": ["cup", "speaker"], "question": "the cup that is close to the speaker. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 88], "object_names": ["cup", "speaker"], "question": "the cup that is near the speaker. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 88], "object_names": ["carpet", "speaker"], "question": "the carpet that is farthest from the speaker. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 88], "object_names": ["carpet", "speaker"], "question": "the carpet that is far from the speaker. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 88], "object_names": ["carpet", "speaker"], "question": "the carpet that is far away from the speaker. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 88], "object_names": ["picture", "speaker"], "question": "the picture that is farthest from the speaker. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 88], "object_names": ["picture", "speaker"], "question": "the picture that is far from the speaker. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["decorative"], "object_ids": [159, 88], "object_names": ["picture", "speaker"], "question": "the picture that is far away from the speaker. What is function of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 88], "object_names": ["towel", "speaker"], "question": "find the towel that is farthest from the speaker. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 88], "object_names": ["towel", "speaker"], "question": "find the towel that is far from the speaker. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 88], "object_names": ["towel", "speaker"], "question": "find the towel that is far away from the speaker. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 98], "object_names": ["table", "computer"], "question": "find the table that is closer to the computer. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 98], "object_names": ["table", "computer"], "question": "find the table that is close to the computer. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["well-maintained"], "object_ids": [36, 98], "object_names": ["table", "computer"], "question": "find the table that is near the computer. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 98], "object_names": ["table", "computer"], "question": "find the table that is farthest from the computer. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 98], "object_names": ["table", "computer"], "question": "find the table that is far from the computer. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 98], "object_names": ["table", "computer"], "question": "find the table that is far away from the computer. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically from the ceiling"], "object_ids": [6, 98], "object_names": ["curtain", "computer"], "question": "the curtain that is closer to the computer. What is placement of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 98], "object_names": ["curtain", "computer"], "question": "the curtain that is close to the computer. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 98], "object_names": ["curtain", "computer"], "question": "the curtain that is near the computer. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 98], "object_names": ["curtain", "computer"], "question": "select the curtain that is farthest from the computer. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 98], "object_names": ["curtain", "computer"], "question": "select the curtain that is far from the computer. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 98], "object_names": ["curtain", "computer"], "question": "select the curtain that is far away from the computer. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 98], "object_names": ["bin", "computer"], "question": "the bin that is closer to the computer. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 98], "object_names": ["bin", "computer"], "question": "the bin that is close to the computer. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 98], "object_names": ["bin", "computer"], "question": "the bin that is near the computer. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [14, 98], "object_names": ["bin", "computer"], "question": "select the bin that is farthest from the computer. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 98], "object_names": ["bin", "computer"], "question": "select the bin that is far from the computer. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [14, 98], "object_names": ["bin", "computer"], "question": "select the bin that is far away from the computer. What is material of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 98], "object_names": ["stool", "computer"], "question": "choose the stool that is closer to the computer. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [29, 98], "object_names": ["stool", "computer"], "question": "choose the stool that is close to the computer. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 98], "object_names": ["stool", "computer"], "question": "choose the stool that is near the computer. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["providing a comfortable seating option for those who want to sit at the bar"], "object_ids": [31, 98], "object_names": ["stool", "computer"], "question": "the stool that is farthest from the computer. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["round seat", "Circular"], "object_ids": [31, 98], "object_names": ["stool", "computer"], "question": "the stool that is far from the computer. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["empty"], "object_ids": [31, 98], "object_names": ["stool", "computer"], "question": "the stool that is far away from the computer. What is state of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [50, 98], "object_names": ["stand", "computer"], "question": "choose the stand that is closer to the computer. What is shape of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 98], "object_names": ["stand", "computer"], "question": "choose the stand that is close to the computer. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 98], "object_names": ["stand", "computer"], "question": "choose the stand that is near the computer. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["flat on the floor"], "object_ids": [162, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "the shoe that is closer to the computer. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [162, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "the shoe that is close to the computer. What is size of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [162, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "the shoe that is near the computer. What is size of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "find the shoe that is farthest from the computer. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["synthetic and leather", "Leather"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "find the shoe that is far from the computer. What is material of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["suitable for everyday wear, sports, or casual outings"], "object_ids": [59, 98], "object_names": ["shoe", "computer"], "question": "find the shoe that is far away from the computer. What is function of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [66, 98], "object_names": ["doorframe", "computer"], "question": "select the doorframe that is farthest from the computer. What is texture of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 98], "object_names": ["doorframe", "computer"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far from the computer. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 98], "object_names": ["doorframe", "computer"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far away from the computer. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 98], "object_names": ["cup", "computer"], "question": "the cup that is closer to the computer. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 98], "object_names": ["cup", "computer"], "question": "the cup that is close to the computer. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["relatively small", "Small"], "object_ids": [147, 98], "object_names": ["cup", "computer"], "question": "the cup that is near the computer. What is size of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 98], "object_names": ["carpet", "computer"], "question": "select the carpet that is farthest from the computer. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 98], "object_names": ["carpet", "computer"], "question": "select the carpet that is far from the computer. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 98], "object_names": ["carpet", "computer"], "question": "select the carpet that is far away from the computer. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 98], "object_names": ["picture", "computer"], "question": "select the picture that is farthest from the computer. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 98], "object_names": ["picture", "computer"], "question": "select the picture that is far from the computer. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 98], "object_names": ["picture", "computer"], "question": "select the picture that is far away from the computer. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["horizontal"], "object_ids": [3, 179], "object_names": ["table", "switch"], "question": "find the table that is closer to the switch. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 179], "object_names": ["table", "switch"], "question": "find the table that is close to the switch. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 179], "object_names": ["table", "switch"], "question": "find the table that is near the switch. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [36, 179], "object_names": ["table", "switch"], "question": "the table that is farthest from the switch. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["light brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [36, 179], "object_names": ["table", "switch"], "question": "the table that is far from the switch. What is color of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 179], "object_names": ["table", "switch"], "question": "the table that is far away from the switch. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [14, 179], "object_names": ["bin", "switch"], "question": "find the bin that is next to the switch. What is shape of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["slightly ajar"], "object_ids": [14, 179], "object_names": ["bin", "switch"], "question": "find the bin that is next to the switch. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [14, 179], "object_names": ["bin", "switch"], "question": "find the bin that is next to the switch. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 179], "object_names": ["bin", "switch"], "question": "find the bin that is farthest from the switch. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 179], "object_names": ["bin", "switch"], "question": "find the bin that is far from the switch. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 179], "object_names": ["bin", "switch"], "question": "find the bin that is far away from the switch. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 179], "object_names": ["backpack", "switch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is closer to the switch. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 179], "object_names": ["backpack", "switch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is close to the switch. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["nylon or similar fabric", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [63, 179], "object_names": ["backpack", "switch"], "question": "choose the backpack that is near the switch. What is material of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 179], "object_names": ["backpack", "switch"], "question": "find the backpack that is farthest from the switch. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 179], "object_names": ["backpack", "switch"], "question": "find the backpack that is far from the switch. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 179], "object_names": ["backpack", "switch"], "question": "find the backpack that is far away from the switch. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 179], "object_names": ["stool", "switch"], "question": "select the stool that is closer to the switch. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["round seat, four legs", "Circular"], "object_ids": [29, 179], "object_names": ["stool", "switch"], "question": "select the stool that is close to the switch. What is shape of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["upright next to the table"], "object_ids": [29, 179], "object_names": ["stool", "switch"], "question": "select the stool that is near the switch. What is placement of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 179], "object_names": ["stool", "switch"], "question": "choose the stool that is farthest from the switch. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [31, 179], "object_names": ["stool", "switch"], "question": "choose the stool that is far from the switch. What is size of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [31, 179], "object_names": ["stool", "switch"], "question": "choose the stool that is far away from the switch. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [31]}, {"answers": ["grainy"], "object_ids": [50, 179], "object_names": ["stand", "switch"], "question": "select the stand that is farthest from the switch. What is texture of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 179], "object_names": ["stand", "switch"], "question": "select the stand that is far from the switch. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 179], "object_names": ["stand", "switch"], "question": "select the stand that is far away from the switch. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is closer to the switch. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is close to the switch. What is size of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 179], "object_names": ["doorframe", "switch"], "question": "choose the doorframe that is near the switch. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "choose the cup that is closer to the switch. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "choose the cup that is close to the switch. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 179], "object_names": ["cup", "switch"], "question": "choose the cup that is near the switch. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 179], "object_names": ["carpet", "switch"], "question": "find the carpet that is closer to the switch. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 179], "object_names": ["carpet", "switch"], "question": "find the carpet that is close to the switch. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["lies flat on the tiled floor"], "object_ids": [150, 179], "object_names": ["carpet", "switch"], "question": "find the carpet that is near the switch. What is placement of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 179], "object_names": ["picture", "switch"], "question": "find the picture that is closer to the switch. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [159, 179], "object_names": ["picture", "switch"], "question": "find the picture that is close to the switch. What is state of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 179], "object_names": ["picture", "switch"], "question": "find the picture that is near the switch. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["cotton or cotton blend", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [180, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "the towel that is next to the switch. What is material of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [180, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "the towel that is next to the switch. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["used for drying hands, dishes, and general kitchen tasks"], "object_ids": [180, 179], "object_names": ["towel", "switch"], "question": "the towel that is next to the switch. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["wood or similar", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 181], "object_names": ["table", "pot"], "question": "the table that is closer to the pot. What is material of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["relatively large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 181], "object_names": ["table", "pot"], "question": "the table that is close to the pot. What is size of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [3, 181], "object_names": ["table", "pot"], "question": "the table that is near the pot. What is texture of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 181], "object_names": ["table", "pot"], "question": "choose the table that is farthest from the pot. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [36, 181], "object_names": ["table", "pot"], "question": "choose the table that is far from the pot. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["on a tiled floor"], "object_ids": [36, 181], "object_names": ["table", "pot"], "question": "choose the table that is far away from the pot. What is placement of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [36]}, {"answers": ["good condition, no tears or stains"], "object_ids": [6, 181], "object_names": ["curtain", "pot"], "question": "find the curtain that is closer to the pot. What is state of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 181], "object_names": ["curtain", "pot"], "question": "find the curtain that is close to the pot. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["cotton or polyester fiber", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 181], "object_names": ["curtain", "pot"], "question": "find the curtain that is near the pot. What is material of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks the light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [7, 181], "object_names": ["curtain", "pot"], "question": "select the curtain that is farthest from the pot. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 181], "object_names": ["curtain", "pot"], "question": "select the curtain that is far from the pot. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["semi-transparent fabric"], "object_ids": [7, 181], "object_names": ["curtain", "pot"], "question": "select the curtain that is far away from the pot. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [15, 181], "object_names": ["bin", "pot"], "question": "select the bin that is farthest from the pot. What is size of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 181], "object_names": ["bin", "pot"], "question": "select the bin that is far from the pot. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["storing small items"], "object_ids": [15, 181], "object_names": ["bin", "pot"], "question": "select the bin that is far away from the pot. What is function of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 181], "object_names": ["backpack", "pot"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the pot. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [19, 181], "object_names": ["backpack", "pot"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the pot. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["leaning against a blue chair"], "object_ids": [19, 181], "object_names": ["backpack", "pot"], "question": "the backpack that is near the pot. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 181], "object_names": ["backpack", "pot"], "question": "find the backpack that is farthest from the pot. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["suitable for daily commuting and traveling"], "object_ids": [63, 181], "object_names": ["backpack", "pot"], "question": "find the backpack that is far from the pot. What is function of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 181], "object_names": ["backpack", "pot"], "question": "find the backpack that is far away from the pot. What is shape of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["provides casual seating or footstool"], "object_ids": [29, 181], "object_names": ["stool", "pot"], "question": "select the stool that is farthest from the pot. What is function of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [29, 181], "object_names": ["stool", "pot"], "question": "select the stool that is far from the pot. What is material of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["natural wood color", "Brown"], "object_ids": [29, 181], "object_names": ["stool", "pot"], "question": "select the stool that is far away from the pot. What is color of the stool ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [29]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 181], "object_names": ["stand", "pot"], "question": "the stand that is farthest from the pot. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 181], "object_names": ["stand", "pot"], "question": "the stand that is far from the pot. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [50, 181], "object_names": ["stand", "pot"], "question": "the stand that is far away from the pot. What is color of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertical"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "find the doorframe that is closer to the pot. What is placement of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "find the doorframe that is close to the pot. What is material of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 181], "object_names": ["doorframe", "pot"], "question": "find the doorframe that is near the pot. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["standing upright on the table"], "object_ids": [147, 181], "object_names": ["cup", "pot"], "question": "the cup that is farthest from the pot. What is placement of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 181], "object_names": ["cup", "pot"], "question": "the cup that is far from the pot. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 181], "object_names": ["cup", "pot"], "question": "the cup that is far away from the pot. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["soft plush"], "object_ids": [150, 181], "object_names": ["carpet", "pot"], "question": "find the carpet that is closer to the pot. What is texture of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["soft plush", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [150, 181], "object_names": ["carpet", "pot"], "question": "find the carpet that is close to the pot. What is material of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["prevents slipping"], "object_ids": [150, 181], "object_names": ["carpet", "pot"], "question": "find the carpet that is near the pot. What is function of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["mainly black and white, with a mix of white and gray", "Black"], "object_ids": [159, 181], "object_names": ["picture", "pot"], "question": "select the picture that is closer to the pot. What is color of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [159, 181], "object_names": ["picture", "pot"], "question": "select the picture that is close to the pot. What is shape of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["medium-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [159, 181], "object_names": ["picture", "pot"], "question": "select the picture that is near the pot. What is size of the picture ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [159]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 181], "object_names": ["towel", "pot"], "question": "choose the towel that is closer to the pot. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 181], "object_names": ["towel", "pot"], "question": "choose the towel that is close to the pot. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 181], "object_names": ["towel", "pot"], "question": "choose the towel that is near the pot. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging on a round towel ring attached to a light blue wall"], "object_ids": [168, 181], "object_names": ["towel", "pot"], "question": "the towel that is farthest from the pot. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["convenient for drying hands"], "object_ids": [168, 181], "object_names": ["towel", "pot"], "question": "the towel that is far from the pot. What is function of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["light green-brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [168, 181], "object_names": ["towel", "pot"], "question": "the towel that is far away from the pot. What is color of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [35, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "select the table that is closer to the lamp. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["in great condition"], "object_ids": [35, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "select the table that is close to the lamp. What is state of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["can be used as a footrest, a seat, or a coffee table"], "object_ids": [35, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "select the table that is near the lamp. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [35]}, {"answers": ["used as a workspace or a place for preparing meals"], "object_ids": [3, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "select the table that is farthest from the lamp. What is function of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "select the table that is far from the lamp. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 189], "object_names": ["table", "lamp"], "question": "select the table that is far away from the lamp. What is shape of the table ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [3]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [6, 189], "object_names": ["curtain", "lamp"], "question": "select the curtain that is closer to the lamp. What is texture of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 189], "object_names": ["curtain", "lamp"], "question": "select the curtain that is close to the lamp. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["blocks light from entering the room"], "object_ids": [6, 189], "object_names": ["curtain", "lamp"], "question": "select the curtain that is near the lamp. What is function of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [6]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 189], "object_names": ["curtain", "lamp"], "question": "the curtain that is farthest from the lamp. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["standard-sized", "Medium"], "object_ids": [7, 189], "object_names": ["curtain", "lamp"], "question": "the curtain that is far from the lamp. What is size of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["light-colored", "White"], "object_ids": [7, 189], "object_names": ["curtain", "lamp"], "question": "the curtain that is far away from the lamp. What is color of the curtain ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [7]}, {"answers": ["on the floor, leaning against a wooden board"], "object_ids": [15, 189], "object_names": ["bin", "lamp"], "question": "select the bin that is closer to the lamp. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["smooth, glossy"], "object_ids": [15, 189], "object_names": ["bin", "lamp"], "question": "select the bin that is close to the lamp. What is texture of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [15, 189], "object_names": ["bin", "lamp"], "question": "select the bin that is near the lamp. What is state of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [15]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 189], "object_names": ["bin", "lamp"], "question": "find the bin that is farthest from the lamp. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["next to a door"], "object_ids": [14, 189], "object_names": ["bin", "lamp"], "question": "find the bin that is far from the lamp. What is placement of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["white", "White"], "object_ids": [14, 189], "object_names": ["bin", "lamp"], "question": "find the bin that is far away from the lamp. What is color of the bin ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [14]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "lamp"], "question": "the backpack that is closer to the lamp. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "lamp"], "question": "the backpack that is close to the lamp. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["good condition"], "object_ids": [19, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "lamp"], "question": "the backpack that is near the lamp. What is state of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [19]}, {"answers": ["medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [63, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "lamp"], "question": "choose the backpack that is farthest from the lamp. What is size of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["laid flat on the bed, slightly tilted"], "object_ids": [63, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "lamp"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far from the lamp. What is placement of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["dark (black or dark grey)", "Black"], "object_ids": [63, 189], "object_names": ["backpack", "lamp"], "question": "choose the backpack that is far away from the lamp. What is color of the backpack ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [63]}, {"answers": ["moderate", "Medium"], "object_ids": [50, 189], "object_names": ["stand", "lamp"], "question": "find the stand that is closer to the lamp. What is size of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["vertically against a wall"], "object_ids": [50, 189], "object_names": ["stand", "lamp"], "question": "find the stand that is close to the lamp. What is placement of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [50, 189], "object_names": ["stand", "lamp"], "question": "find the stand that is near the lamp. What is material of the stand ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [50]}, {"answers": ["synthetic and leather", "Leather"], "object_ids": [59, 189], "object_names": ["shoe", "lamp"], "question": "select the shoe that is closer to the lamp. What is material of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["vertically on the floor, slightly tilted to the right"], "object_ids": [59, 189], "object_names": ["shoe", "lamp"], "question": "select the shoe that is close to the lamp. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["synthetic and leather", "Leather"], "object_ids": [59, 189], "object_names": ["shoe", "lamp"], "question": "select the shoe that is near the lamp. What is material of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [59]}, {"answers": ["flat on the floor"], "object_ids": [162, 189], "object_names": ["shoe", "lamp"], "question": "the shoe that is farthest from the lamp. What is placement of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["black and white", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [162, 189], "object_names": ["shoe", "lamp"], "question": "the shoe that is far from the lamp. What is color of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["smooth"], "object_ids": [162, 189], "object_names": ["shoe", "lamp"], "question": "the shoe that is far away from the lamp. What is texture of the shoe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [162]}, {"answers": ["closed"], "object_ids": [66, 189], "object_names": ["doorframe", "lamp"], "question": "select the doorframe that is farthest from the lamp. What is state of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": [{"doorframe": "light brown", "door": "white"}, "More than one color"], "object_ids": [66, 189], "object_names": ["doorframe", "lamp"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far from the lamp. What is color of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [66, 189], "object_names": ["doorframe", "lamp"], "question": "select the doorframe that is far away from the lamp. What is shape of the doorframe ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [66]}, {"answers": ["serves as a basic everyday item for holding liquids"], "object_ids": [147, 189], "object_names": ["cup", "lamp"], "question": "choose the cup that is farthest from the lamp. What is function of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [147, 189], "object_names": ["cup", "lamp"], "question": "choose the cup that is far from the lamp. What is color of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [147, 189], "object_names": ["cup", "lamp"], "question": "choose the cup that is far away from the lamp. What is material of the cup ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [147]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 189], "object_names": ["carpet", "lamp"], "question": "the carpet that is farthest from the lamp. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [150, 189], "object_names": ["carpet", "lamp"], "question": "the carpet that is far from the lamp. What is shape of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["deep blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [150, 189], "object_names": ["carpet", "lamp"], "question": "the carpet that is far away from the lamp. What is color of the carpet ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [150]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 189], "object_names": ["towel", "lamp"], "question": "the towel that is closer to the lamp. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [180, 189], "object_names": ["towel", "lamp"], "question": "the towel that is close to the lamp. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["hanging vertically on door handle"], "object_ids": [180, 189], "object_names": ["towel", "lamp"], "question": "the towel that is near the lamp. What is placement of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [180]}, {"answers": ["rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [168, 189], "object_names": ["towel", "lamp"], "question": "select the towel that is farthest from the lamp. What is shape of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["neatly folded"], "object_ids": [168, 189], "object_names": ["towel", "lamp"], "question": "select the towel that is far from the lamp. What is state of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["standard", "Medium"], "object_ids": [168, 189], "object_names": ["towel", "lamp"], "question": "select the towel that is far away from the lamp. What is size of the towel ?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": null, "output_bboxes_id": [168]}, {"answers": ["The table is used for sitting at the stool."], "object_ids": ["3", "29"], "object_names": ["table", "stool"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["3", "29"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["The stool is used for sitting at the table."], "object_ids": ["30", "3"], "object_names": ["stool", "table"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["30", "3"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["The table is used for sitting at the stool."], "object_ids": ["3", "31"], "object_names": ["table", "stool"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["3", "31"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["The table is used for sitting at the stool."], "object_ids": ["3", "32"], "object_names": ["table", "stool"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["3", "32"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["The table is placed on cup to hold a beverage which can be enjoyed while sitting on the stools."], "object_ids": ["3", "154"], "object_names": ["table", "cup"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["3", "154"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["The table is placed on object for functional or decorative purposes."], "object_ids": ["3", "155"], "object_names": ["table", "object"], "question": "What is the function relationship between these two objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["3", "155"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Belong to the class of dining furniture, together they form a dining set used for eating and socializing."], "object_ids": ["3", "29", "30", "31", "32"], "object_names": ["table", "stool", "stool", "stool", "stool"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 5 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["3", "29", "30", "31", "32"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Belong to the class of tableware."], "object_ids": ["154", "3"], "object_names": ["cup", "table"], "question": "What is the joint function between these 2 objects in the dining region?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": ["154", "3"], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the pillow and the stool are both Furniture"], "object_ids": [17, 29], "object_names": ["pillow", "stool"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17, 29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the switch and the remote control are both Electronics"], "object_ids": [179, 123], "object_names": ["switch", "remote control"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [179, 123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the curtain and the picture are both Decorations"], "object_ids": [7, 161], "object_names": ["curtain", "picture"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7, 161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the basket and the object are both Store and organize supplies"], "object_ids": [47, 61], "object_names": ["basket", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47, 61], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the bowl and the toaster are both Kitchenware"], "object_ids": [184, 54], "object_names": ["bowl", "toaster"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184, 54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the shoe and the shower are both Personal-care supply"], "object_ids": [59, 5], "object_names": ["shoe", "shower"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59, 5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the speaker and the clock are both Entertainment and leisure equipment"], "object_ids": [88, 18], "object_names": ["speaker", "clock"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88, 18], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the remote control is Entertainment and leisure equipment and the curtain is Decorations"], "object_ids": [122, 7], "object_names": ["remote control", "curtain"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122, 7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the refrigerator is Electronics and the bowl is Kitchenware"], "object_ids": [34, 184], "object_names": ["refrigerator", "bowl"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34, 184], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the tissue box is Store and organize supplies and the towel is Decorations"], "object_ids": [49, 180], "object_names": ["tissue box", "towel"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49, 180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the towel is Decorations and the shoe is Personal-care supply"], "object_ids": [180, 162], "object_names": ["towel", "shoe"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [180, 162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the shoe is Personal-care supply and the curtain is Decorations"], "object_ids": [162, 7], "object_names": ["shoe", "curtain"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [162, 7], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the toaster is Kitchenware and the picture is Decorations"], "object_ids": [54, 161], "object_names": ["toaster", "picture"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [54, 161], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the remote control is Entertainment and leisure equipment and the basket is Store and organize supplies"], "object_ids": [122, 47], "object_names": ["remote control", "basket"], "question": "Are these two objects same in coarse_grained_category? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122, 47], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Their same coarse_grained_category is Furniture", "Furniture"], "object_ids": [3, 4, 6, 8, 9, 12, 17, 29, 30, 31, 32, 35, 36, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 50, 55, 60, 66, 68, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 157], "object_names": ["table", "counter", "curtain", "desk", "cabinet", "scale", "pillow", "stool", "stool", "stool", "stool", "table", "table", "bed", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "stand", "door", "object", "doorframe", "chair", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the coarse_grained_category?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 6, 8, 9, 17, 29, 30, 31, 32, 35, 36, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 50, 55, 60, 66, 68, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 157]}, {"answers": ["Their same coarse_grained_category is Electronics", "Electronics"], "object_ids": [16, 34, 123, 179], "object_names": ["tv", "refrigerator", "remote control", "switch"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the coarse_grained_category?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": [16, 123, 179]}, {"answers": ["Their same coarse_grained_category is Decorations", "Decorations"], "object_ids": [7, 150, 159, 161, 180], "object_names": ["curtain", "carpet", "picture", "picture", "towel"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the coarse_grained_category?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [150], "output_bboxes_id": [7, 159, 161, 180]}, {"answers": ["Their same coarse_grained_category is Store and organize supplies", "Store and organize supplies"], "object_ids": [13, 14, 15, 47, 49, 61, 147], "object_names": ["bin", "bin", "bin", "basket", "tissue box", "object", "cup"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the coarse_grained_category?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47], "output_bboxes_id": [13, 14, 15, 49, 61, 147]}, {"answers": ["Their same coarse_grained_category is Kitchenware", "Kitchenware"], "object_ids": [54, 182, 183, 184], "object_names": ["toaster", "object", "bowl", "bowl"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the coarse_grained_category?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": [54, 182, 183]}, {"answers": ["Their same coarse_grained_category is Personal-care supply", "Personal-care supply"], "object_ids": [5, 11, 19, 37, 59, 63, 162, 165, 168], "object_names": ["shower", "sink", "backpack", "toilet", "shoe", "backpack", "shoe", "object", "towel"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the coarse_grained_category?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37], "output_bboxes_id": [5, 11, 19, 59, 63, 162, 165, 168]}, {"answers": ["Their same coarse_grained_category is Entertainment and leisure equipment", "Entertainment and leisure equipment"], "object_ids": [18, 48, 58, 88, 122, 178], "object_names": ["clock", "guitar", "bicycle", "speaker", "remote control", "object"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the coarse_grained_category?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [58], "output_bboxes_id": [18, 48, 88, 122, 178]}, {"answers": ["No, the pillow and the pillow are both Blue"], "object_ids": [157, 132], "object_names": ["pillow", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157, 132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the chair and the backpack are both Black"], "object_ids": [68, 63], "object_names": ["chair", "backpack"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68, 63], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the toilet and the curtain are both White"], "object_ids": [37, 6], "object_names": ["toilet", "curtain"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37, 6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the pillow and the pillow are both Gray"], "object_ids": [131, 134], "object_names": ["pillow", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131, 134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the stool and the cabinet are both Brown"], "object_ids": [31, 42], "object_names": ["stool", "cabinet"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [31, 42], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the remote control and the shoe are both More than one color"], "object_ids": [122, 162], "object_names": ["remote control", "shoe"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122, 162], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the pillow is Gray and the bed is Blue"], "object_ids": [134, 38], "object_names": ["pillow", "bed"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134, 38], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the basket is Blue and the object is White"], "object_ids": [47, 182], "object_names": ["basket", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47, 182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the speaker is Black and the cabinet is Brown"], "object_ids": [88, 41], "object_names": ["speaker", "cabinet"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [88, 41], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the doorframe is More than one color and the table is Blue"], "object_ids": [66, 35], "object_names": ["doorframe", "table"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66, 35], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the remote control is More than one color and the object is Black"], "object_ids": [123, 178], "object_names": ["remote control", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [123, 178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the pillow is Blue and the remote control is More than one color"], "object_ids": [157, 123], "object_names": ["pillow", "remote control"], "question": "Are these two objects same in color? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [157, 123], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Their same color is Blue", "Blue"], "object_ids": [35, 38, 47, 124, 132, 147, 150, 157], "object_names": ["table", "bed", "basket", "pillow", "pillow", "cup", "carpet", "pillow"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the color?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [124], "output_bboxes_id": [35, 38, 47, 132, 147, 150, 157]}, {"answers": ["Their same color is Black", "Black"], "object_ids": [16, 19, 59, 61, 63, 68, 88, 133, 159, 165, 178, 189], "object_names": ["tv", "backpack", "shoe", "object", "backpack", "chair", "speaker", "pillow", "picture", "object", "object", "lamp"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the color?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [61], "output_bboxes_id": [16, 19, 59, 63, 68, 88, 133, 159, 165, 178, 189]}, {"answers": ["Their same color is White", "White"], "object_ids": [3, 6, 7, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 18, 34, 37, 40, 49, 50, 54, 55, 135, 161, 172, 179, 180, 182, 183, 184, 186], "object_names": ["table", "curtain", "curtain", "sink", "scale", "bin", "bin", "bin", "clock", "refrigerator", "toilet", "cabinet", "tissue box", "stand", "toaster", "door", "pillow", "picture", "paper", "switch", "towel", "object", "bowl", "bowl", "object"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the color?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186], "output_bboxes_id": [3, 6, 7, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 18, 34, 37, 40, 49, 50, 54, 55, 135, 161, 172, 179, 180, 182, 183, 184]}, {"answers": ["Their same color is Gray", "Gray"], "object_ids": [131, 134], "object_names": ["pillow", "pillow"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the color?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [134], "output_bboxes_id": [131]}, {"answers": ["Their same color is Brown", "Brown"], "object_ids": [4, 8, 17, 29, 30, 31, 32, 36, 39, 41, 42, 43, 44, 48, 168], "object_names": ["counter", "desk", "pillow", "stool", "stool", "stool", "stool", "table", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "guitar", "towel"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the color?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [168], "output_bboxes_id": [4, 8, 17, 29, 30, 31, 32, 36, 39, 41, 42, 43, 44, 48]}, {"answers": ["Their same color is More than one color", "More than one color"], "object_ids": [60, 66, 121, 122, 123, 162], "object_names": ["object", "doorframe", "remote control", "remote control", "remote control", "shoe"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the color?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [122], "output_bboxes_id": [60, 66, 121, 123, 162]}, {"answers": ["No, the guitar and the cabinet are both Wood"], "object_ids": [48, 44], "object_names": ["guitar", "cabinet"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [48, 44], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the refrigerator and the bicycle are both Metal"], "object_ids": [34, 58], "object_names": ["refrigerator", "bicycle"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34, 58], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the remote control and the object are both Plastic"], "object_ids": [121, 182], "object_names": ["remote control", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121, 182], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the pillow and the curtain are both Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [131, 6], "object_names": ["pillow", "curtain"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [131, 6], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the bowl and the toilet are both Ceramic"], "object_ids": [184, 37], "object_names": ["bowl", "toilet"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184, 37], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the tv is Plastic and the cabinet is Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [16, 40], "object_names": ["tv", "cabinet"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [16, 40], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the toilet is Ceramic and the refrigerator is Metal"], "object_ids": [37, 34], "object_names": ["toilet", "refrigerator"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [37, 34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the object is Fabric/Feather and the refrigerator is Metal"], "object_ids": [60, 34], "object_names": ["object", "refrigerator"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60, 34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the sink is Ceramic and the object is Plastic"], "object_ids": [11, 165], "object_names": ["sink", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11, 165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the sink is Ceramic and the towel is Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [11, 180], "object_names": ["sink", "towel"], "question": "Are these two objects same in material? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11, 180], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Their same material is Wood", "Wood"], "object_ids": [3, 8, 9, 18, 29, 30, 31, 32, 36, 38, 39, 41, 42, 43, 44, 48, 50, 55, 66], "object_names": ["table", "desk", "cabinet", "clock", "stool", "stool", "stool", "stool", "table", "bed", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "guitar", "stand", "door", "doorframe"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the material?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [66], "output_bboxes_id": [3, 8, 9, 18, 29, 30, 31, 32, 36, 38, 39, 41, 42, 43, 44, 48, 50, 55]}, {"answers": ["Their same material is Metal", "Metal"], "object_ids": [12, 34, 54, 58, 68, 178, 189], "object_names": ["scale", "refrigerator", "toaster", "bicycle", "chair", "object", "lamp"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the material?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [34], "output_bboxes_id": [12, 54, 58, 68, 178, 189]}, {"answers": ["Their same material is Plastic", "Plastic"], "object_ids": [13, 14, 15, 16, 121, 122, 123, 147, 162, 165, 179, 182], "object_names": ["bin", "bin", "bin", "tv", "remote control", "remote control", "remote control", "cup", "shoe", "object", "switch", "object"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the material?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [165], "output_bboxes_id": [13, 14, 15, 16, 121, 122, 123, 147, 162, 179, 182]}, {"answers": ["Their same material is Fabric/Feather", "Fabric/Feather"], "object_ids": [6, 7, 19, 35, 40, 47, 49, 60, 61, 63, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 150, 157, 161, 168, 180], "object_names": ["curtain", "curtain", "backpack", "table", "cabinet", "basket", "tissue box", "object", "object", "backpack", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "carpet", "pillow", "picture", "towel", "towel"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the material?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63], "output_bboxes_id": [6, 7, 19, 35, 40, 47, 49, 60, 61, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 150, 157, 161, 168, 180]}, {"answers": ["Their same material is Ceramic", "Ceramic"], "object_ids": [11, 37, 183, 184], "object_names": ["sink", "toilet", "bowl", "bowl"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the material?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": [37, 183, 184]}, {"answers": ["No, the backpack and the pillow are both Rectangular"], "object_ids": [63, 132], "object_names": ["backpack", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [63, 132], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the stool and the sink are both Circular"], "object_ids": [32, 11], "object_names": ["stool", "sink"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [32, 11], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the object and the object are both Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [186, 178], "object_names": ["object", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186, 178], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the shoe and the object are both Spherical"], "object_ids": [59, 165], "object_names": ["shoe", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [59, 165], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the object and the bin are both Cuboid"], "object_ids": [60, 13], "object_names": ["object", "bin"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60, 13], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the basket is Cylindrical and the pillow is Rectangular"], "object_ids": [47, 124], "object_names": ["basket", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [47, 124], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the object is Cylindrical and the shoe is Spherical"], "object_ids": [186, 59], "object_names": ["object", "shoe"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [186, 59], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the cabinet is Rectangular and the bowl is Circular"], "object_ids": [9, 183], "object_names": ["cabinet", "bowl"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [9, 183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the bowl is Spherical and the object is Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [184, 186], "object_names": ["bowl", "object"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184, 186], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the bin is Cuboid and the cabinet is Rectangular"], "object_ids": [13, 9], "object_names": ["bin", "cabinet"], "question": "Are these two objects same in shape? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [13, 9], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Their same shape is Rectangular", "Rectangular"], "object_ids": [3, 4, 5, 7, 8, 9, 12, 14, 15, 16, 17, 19, 34, 35, 36, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 49, 50, 54, 55, 61, 63, 66, 68, 88, 121, 122, 123, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 150, 157, 159, 161, 168, 172, 179, 180, 182], "object_names": ["table", "counter", "shower", "curtain", "desk", "cabinet", "scale", "bin", "bin", "tv", "pillow", "backpack", "refrigerator", "table", "table", "bed", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "tissue box", "stand", "toaster", "door", "object", "backpack", "doorframe", "chair", "speaker", "remote control", "remote control", "remote control", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "carpet", "pillow", "picture", "picture", "towel", "paper", "switch", "towel", "object"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the shape?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": [3, 4, 5, 7, 8, 9, 12, 14, 15, 16, 17, 19, 34, 35, 36, 38, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 49, 50, 54, 55, 61, 63, 66, 68, 88, 121, 122, 123, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 150, 157, 159, 161, 168, 172, 179, 180, 182]}, {"answers": ["Their same shape is Circular", "Circular"], "object_ids": [11, 18, 29, 30, 31, 32, 37, 183], "object_names": ["sink", "clock", "stool", "stool", "stool", "stool", "toilet", "bowl"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the shape?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [11], "output_bboxes_id": [18, 29, 30, 31, 32, 37, 183]}, {"answers": ["Their same shape is Cylindrical", "Cylindrical"], "object_ids": [47, 48, 178, 186], "object_names": ["basket", "guitar", "object", "object"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the shape?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [178], "output_bboxes_id": [47, 48, 186]}, {"answers": ["Their same shape is Spherical", "Spherical"], "object_ids": [59, 165, 184], "object_names": ["shoe", "object", "bowl"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the shape?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [184], "output_bboxes_id": [59, 165]}, {"answers": ["Their same shape is Cuboid", "Cuboid"], "object_ids": [13, 60], "object_names": ["bin", "object"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the shape?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [60], "output_bboxes_id": [13]}, {"answers": ["No, the chair and the scale are both Medium"], "object_ids": [68, 12], "object_names": ["chair", "scale"], "question": "Are these two objects same in weight? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [68, 12], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the lamp and the toaster are both Light"], "object_ids": [189, 54], "object_names": ["lamp", "toaster"], "question": "Are these two objects same in weight? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189, 54], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the scale is Medium and the shower is Light"], "object_ids": [12, 5], "object_names": ["scale", "shower"], "question": "Are these two objects same in weight? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12, 5], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the shower is Light and the stool is Medium"], "object_ids": [5, 29], "object_names": ["shower", "stool"], "question": "Are these two objects same in weight? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [5, 29], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Their same weight is Medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [12, 29, 68, 178], "object_names": ["scale", "stool", "chair", "object"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the weight?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [12], "output_bboxes_id": [29, 68, 178]}, {"answers": ["Their same weight is Light", "Light"], "object_ids": [5, 54, 189], "object_names": ["shower", "toaster", "lamp"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the weight?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [189], "output_bboxes_id": [5, 54]}, {"answers": ["No, the pillow and the refrigerator are both Large"], "object_ids": [17, 34], "object_names": ["pillow", "refrigerator"], "question": "Are these two objects same in size? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [17, 34], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the remote control and the pillow are both Medium"], "object_ids": [121, 134], "object_names": ["remote control", "pillow"], "question": "Are these two objects same in size? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [121, 134], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the tissue box and the switch are both Small"], "object_ids": [49, 179], "object_names": ["tissue box", "switch"], "question": "Are these two objects same in size? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [49, 179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the door is Medium and the cabinet is Large"], "object_ids": [55, 39], "object_names": ["door", "cabinet"], "question": "Are these two objects same in size? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [55, 39], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the paper is Small and the bowl is Medium"], "object_ids": [172, 183], "object_names": ["paper", "bowl"], "question": "Are these two objects same in size? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172, 183], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["No, the cabinet is Medium and the switch is Small"], "object_ids": [40, 179], "object_names": ["cabinet", "switch"], "question": "Are these two objects same in size? Why?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [40, 179], "output_bboxes_id": null}, {"answers": ["Their same size is Large", "Large"], "object_ids": [3, 17, 34, 35, 39, 41], "object_names": ["table", "pillow", "refrigerator", "table", "cabinet", "cabinet"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the size?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [39], "output_bboxes_id": [3, 17, 34, 35, 41]}, {"answers": ["Their same size is Medium", "Medium"], "object_ids": [4, 6, 7, 8, 9, 11, 12, 14, 15, 16, 18, 19, 29, 30, 31, 32, 36, 37, 40, 42, 43, 44, 47, 48, 50, 54, 55, 58, 59, 61, 63, 66, 68, 88, 121, 122, 123, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 150, 157, 159, 161, 162, 165, 168, 178, 180, 182, 183, 184, 186, 189], "object_names": ["counter", "curtain", "curtain", "desk", "cabinet", "sink", "scale", "bin", "bin", "tv", "clock", "backpack", "stool", "stool", "stool", "stool", "table", "toilet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "cabinet", "basket", "guitar", "stand", "toaster", "door", "bicycle", "shoe", "object", "backpack", "doorframe", "chair", "speaker", "remote control", "remote control", "remote control", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "pillow", "carpet", "pillow", "picture", "picture", "shoe", "object", "towel", "object", "towel", "object", "bowl", "bowl", "object", "lamp"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the size?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [7], "output_bboxes_id": [4, 6, 8, 9, 11, 12, 14, 15, 16, 18, 19, 29, 30, 31, 32, 36, 37, 40, 42, 43, 44, 47, 48, 50, 54, 55, 58, 59, 61, 63, 66, 68, 88, 121, 122, 123, 124, 131, 132, 133, 134, 135, 150, 157, 159, 161, 162, 165, 168, 178, 180, 182, 183, 184, 186, 189]}, {"answers": ["Their same size is Small", "Small"], "object_ids": [5, 13, 38, 49, 147, 172, 179], "object_names": ["shower", "bin", "bed", "tissue box", "cup", "paper", "switch"], "question": "What other objects are same as this object in the size?", "scan_id": "scene0000_00", "input_bboxes_id": [172], "output_bboxes_id": [5, 13, 38, 49, 147, 179]}]